<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Matthias Klumpp -->
<component type="console-application">
  <id>org.freedesktop.appstream.cli</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>

  <name>AppStream CLI</name>

  <name xml:lang="cs">Textové uživatelské rozhraní pro AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="de">AppStream CLI</name>

  <name xml:lang="fi">AppStream-komentorivityökalu</name>

  <name xml:lang="fr">Interface en ligne de commande AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="id">CLI AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="it">CLI AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="lt">AppStream komandų eilutė</name>

  <name xml:lang="nl">AppStream-CLI</name>

  <name xml:lang="pl">Interfejs AppStream dla wiersza poleceń</name>

  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">CLI do AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="ru">AppStream CLI-программа</name>

  <name xml:lang="tr">AppStream CLI</name>

  <name xml:lang="uk">Командний рядок AppStream</name>

  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">AppStream 命令行界面</name>

  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">AppStream 命令列介面</name>
  <summary>An utility to work with AppStream metadata</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro práci s AppStream metadaty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug für AppStream Metadaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un utilitaire travaillant sur les métadonnées AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Uno strumento per lavorare con metadati AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Paslaugų programa, skirta darbui su AppStream metaduomenimis</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel om te werken met AppStream-metagegevens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do działania z metadanymi AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um utilitário para trabalhar com os metadatas do AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Утилита для работы с метаданными AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для обробки метаданих AppStream</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">用于操作 AppStream 元数据的实用工具</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">處理 AppStream 中介資料的公用程式</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      AppStream is a cross-distribution specification to provide metadata about software components.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">AppStream je standard pro poskytování metadat o programovém vybavení, používaný napříč linuxovými distribucemi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">AppStream ist eine distributionsunabhängige Spezifikation um Metadaten zu Softwarekomponenten bereitzustellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Appstream est une spécification multi-distribution qui fournit des métadonnées concernant les composants logiciels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">AppStream è una specifica multi-distribuzione che fornisce metadati riguardo ai componenti software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">AppStream is een distributie-onafhankelijke specificatie die metagegevens beschikbaar stelt over software-onderdelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">AppStream to specyfikacja używana przez wiele dystrybucji do dostarczania metadanych o składnikach oprogramowania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">AppStream é uma especificação independente de distribuição para provimento de metadados sobre componentes de software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">AppStream — это кросс-платформенная спецификация предоставления метаданных о программных компонентах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">AppStream — багатоплатформова специфікація надання метаданих щодо компонентів програмного забезпечення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">AppStream 为一个跨散布版的规范，旨在提供软件组件的元数据。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">AppStream 為一個跨散佈版的規範，旨在提供軟體組件的中介資料。</p>
    <p>
      This tool allows reading, writing, validating and transforming AppStream XML or YAML metadata.
      It also allows accessing the system metadata pool to for example query for software providing a
      specific mimetype and installing it by its software component identifier.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tento nástroj umožňuje čtení, zápis, ověřování a přeměnu AppStream XML nebo YAML metadat. Také zpřístupňuje systémový fond metadat pro například dotazování se na software, poskytující konkrétní MIME typ a jeho instalaci na základě identifikátoru softwarové součásti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cet outil permet la lecture, l'écriture, la validation et la transformation des métadonnées XML ou YAML d'AppStream. Il permet également d'accéder à l'ensemble de métadonnées système pour, par exemple, chercher un logiciel supportant un type mime spécifique et l'installer en utilisant son identifiant de composant logiciel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questo strumento consente di leggere, scrivere, validare e trasformare metadati AppStream XML o YAML. Consente inoltre di accedere all'insieme dei metadati del sistema per, per esempio, eseguire ricerche su un software che fornisce uno specifico tipo di MIME e installarlo attraverso il suo identificativo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit hulpprogramma stelt u in staat AppStream XML of YAML-metagegevens te lezen, schrijven, valideren en wijzigen. Het stelt u tevens in staat om toegang te krijgen tot de systeem-metagegevenspool. U kunt daar bijv. zoeken naar software die een bepaald mimetype aanbiedt en deze installeren middels de ID.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">To narzędzie umożliwia odczytywanie, zapisywanie, sprawdzanie poprawności i przekształcanie metadanych AppStream w językach XML i YAML. Umożliwia także dostęp do puli metadanych systemu, aby na przykład wyszukać oprogramowanie dostarczające podany typ MIME i zainstalować je za pomocą jego identyfikatora składnika oprogramowania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Эта утилита позволяет читать, записывать, проверять и преобразовывать метаданные AppStream в формате XML или YAML. Она также позволяет доступ к системному пулу метаданных, например, для запроса ПО, работающего с определённым типом файлов, и его установки по идентификатору программного компонента.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цієї програми ви зможете читати, записувати, перевіряти та перетворювати метадані AppStream у форматах XML і YAML. Також за її допомогою можна отримувати доступ до буфера загальносистемних метаданих, наприклад, для того, щоб визначити програмне забезпечення для обробки даних певного типу MIME та його встановлення за ідентифікатором компонента програмного забезпечення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">本工具可用于读写、验证与变换 AppStream XML 或 YAML 元数据；此外还可访问系统元数据库，进行诸如搜索提供某种 mime 类型的软件，并按照其软件组件辨识码安装。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">本工具可用於讀寫、驗證與變換 AppStream XML 或 YAML 中介資料；此外還可存取系統中介資料庫，進行諸如搜尋提供某種 mime 類型的軟體，並按照其軟體組件辨識碼安裝。</p>
  </description>

  <url type="homepage">http://www.freedesktop.org/wiki/Distributions/AppStream/</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.freedesktop.org/software/appstream/docs/chap-AppStream-ManualPages.html</url>

  <project_group>Freedesktop</project_group>

  <translation type="gettext">appstream</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>appstreamcli</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
