<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.Weather.Application.desktop</id>
  <name>Weather</name>
  <name xml:lang="an">Orache</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الطقس</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">বতৰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Надвор'е</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Прогноза</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Vrijeme</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Meteorologia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Weather</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Počasí</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Vejr</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Wetter</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Καιρός</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Weather</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Vetero</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Meteorología</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Ilm</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Eguraldia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">آب‌وهوا</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Sää</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Météo</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Meteo</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Aimsir</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Aimsir</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Clima</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">מזג האוויר</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Időjárás</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Cuaca</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Veður</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Meteo</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">天気</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Ауа райы</name>
  <name xml:lang="kn">ಹವಾಮಾನ</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">날씨</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Orai</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Laikapstākļi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">കാലാവസ്ഥ</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Vær</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">मौसम</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Weer</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Metèo</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੌਸਮ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Pogoda</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Metereologia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Meteorologia</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Vremea</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Погода</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Počasie</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Vreme</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Време</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Vreme</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Väder</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">వాతావరణం</name>
  <name xml:lang="tg">Обу ҳаво</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">รายงานอากาศ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Hava Durumu</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Погода</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Thời tiết</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">天气</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">天氣</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">天氣</name>
  <summary>Show weather conditions and forecast</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="an">Amostrar as condicions meteorolochicas y o pronostico</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">اعرض حالة الطقس و النشرة الجوية</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">বতৰৰ অৱস্থা আৰু পূৰ্বানুমান দেখুৱাওক</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Прагляд звестак аб надвор'і і яго прагноз</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Показване на метеорологичното време и прогноза</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Prikaži vremenske uslove i prognozu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mostra les condicions actuals i la predicció meteorològica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Mostra les condicions actuals i la previsió meteorològica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zobrazte si povětrnostní podmínky a předpověď počasí</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Vis vejrforhold og -udsigt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Wetterberichte und -vorhersagen anzeigen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εμφάνιση συνθηκών καιρού και πρόβλεψης</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Show weather conditions and forecast</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Montras veterajn statojn kaj prognozojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Mostrar las condiciones meteorológicas y el pronóstico</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Ilmaolude ja ilmateate kuvamine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Erakutsi eguraldiaren egoera eta iragarpena</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">نمایش وضعیت و پیش‌بینی آب‌وهوا</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Näytä säätiedot ja -ennuste</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Affiche le temps qu'il fait et les prévisions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Mostre condizions e previsions meteo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ga">Taispeáin staid agus réamhaisnéis na haimsire</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Seall an aimsir an-dràsta agus ro-aithris</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Mostrar as condicións e predicións do tmepo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הצגת תנאים ואת תחזית מזג האוויר</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Időjárási viszonyok és előrejelzés megjelenítése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Tampilkan kondisi dan ramalan cuaca</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Birta veðurslýsingar og veðurspár</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Mostra condizioni e previsioni meteo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">天気の概況と予報を表示します</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Ауа райының күйін және болжамын көрсету</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">날씨와 일기 예보 보기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Rodyti orų sąlygas ir prognozes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Rādīt laikapstākļu prognozi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">കാലാവസ്ഥയുടെ നിഅയും പ്രവചനവും കാണിക്കുക</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Vis værforhold og værmelding</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">हालको मौसम अवस्था अनुगमन गर्दछ, र पूर्वानुमान गर्दछ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Weersomstandigheden en -verwachtingen tonen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Aficha lo temps que fa e las previsions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਮੌਸਮ ਹਾਲਤ ਅਤੇ ਭਵਿੱਖਬਾਣੀ ਵੇਖੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie warunków pogodowych i prognozy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Mostra as condições metereológicas e previsões</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Mostra condições meteorológicas e previsão do tempo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Afișează prognoza și condițiile meteorologice</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Показать погодные условия и прогноз</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobrazuje poveternostné podmienky a predpoveď počasia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Spremljanje trenutnih vremenskih razmer in napovedi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Прикажите временске прилике и прогнозу</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Prikažite vremenske prilike i prognozu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visar prognoser och väderförhållanden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">వాతావరణ పరిస్థితులను, సూచినలను చూపించు</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tg">Намоиш додани шароит ва пешгӯии обу ҳаво</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">แสดงสภาพอากาศและการพยากรณ์</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Hava durumunu ve tahminleri göster</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Показувати погодні умови і прогноз</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Xem tình hình thời tiết và dự báo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">显示天气状况和天气预报</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">顯示天氣狀況與氣象預報</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">顯示天氣狀況與氣象預報</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and CC-BY-3.0 and CC-BY-SA-3.0</project_license>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <description>
    <p>A small application that allows you to monitor the current weather conditions for your city, or anywhere in the world.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">Una chicota aplicación que le permite monitorizar l'orache actual en a suya ciudat, u en qualsiquier puesto d'o mundo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تطبيق صغير يتيح لك مراقبة حالات الطقس الحالية لمدينتك أو أي مدينة تريدها في العالم.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">এটা সৰু এপ্লিকেচন যি আপোনাক আপোনাৰ নগৰ, অথবা পৃথিৱীৰ যিকোনো ঠাইত বৰ্তমান বতৰ অৱস্থা পৰ্যবেক্ষণ কৰাৰ অনুমতি দিয়ে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Малка програма за наблюдение на текущото метеорологично време в града ви или някъде другаде по света.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Mala aplikacija koja dopušta prikaz trenutnih vremenskih uslova za vaš grad, ili bilo gdje u svijetu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Un programa petit que us permet fer un seguiment de les condicions meteorològiques actuals a la vostra ciutat o a qualsevol lloc del món.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Un programa petit que vos permet fer un seguiment de les condicions meteorològiques actuals a la vostra ciutat o a qualsevol lloc del món.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Malá aplikace, díky které můžete sledovat aktuální povětrnostní podmínky ve svém městě nebo kdekoliv na světě.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Et lille program, som giver dig mulighed for at overvåge de nuværende vejrforhold i din by, eller hvor som helst i verden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Eine kleine Anwendung, welche es Ihnen erlaubt, das aktuelle Wetter für Ihre Stadt oder für einen beliebigen Ort auf der Welt zu betrachten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μια μικρή εφαρμογή που σας επιτρέπει να παρακολουθείτε τις τρέχουσες καιρικές συνθήκες για την πόλη σας, ή για οποιαδήποτε άλλη τοποθεσία στον κόσμο.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Eta aplikaĵo kiu permesas al vi observi la nunan veterajn kondiĉojn de via urbo, aŭ ie ajn en la mondo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Una pequeña aplicación que le permite monitorizar el tiempo actual en su ciudad, o en cualquier lugar del mundo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Aplikazio txiki bat da, zure herriko edo munduko beste leku bateko uneko eguraldiaren berri ematen dizuna.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">یک برنامه کوچک که به شما اجازه می‌دهد تا وضعیت آب‌وهوایی شهر خود یا هرجایی در دنیا را بررسی کنید.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Pieni sovellus, joka mahdollistaa kotikaupunkisi tai minkä tahansa muun sijainnin säätietojen hakemisen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Une petite application qui vous permet de surveiller les conditions météo dans votre ville ou n'importe où dans le monde.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Une piçule aplicazion che a permet di tegnî di voli lis condizions meteo atuâi de tô citât, o cualsisei puest intal mont.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ga">Feidhmchláirín a ligeann duit monatóireacht a dhéanamh ar aimsir reatha do cathrach, nó aimsir aon áite eile sa domhan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Aplacaid bheag a leigeas leat sùil a chumail air staid na h-aimsire sa bhaile agad no àite sam bith air an t-saoghal.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Un pequeno aplicativo que lle permitirá facer un seguimento das condicións meteorolóxicas actuais da súa cidade, ou calquera lugar do mundo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יישום קטן המאפשר לך לצפות בתנאי מזג האוויר הנוכחיים בעיר שלך או בכל מקום אחר בעולם.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Egy kicsi alkalmazás, amely lehető teszi a jelenlegi időjárási körülmények figyelését a településén, vagy bárhol a világon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Aplikasi kecil yang memungkinkan Anda memantau kondisi cuaca saat ini untuk kota Anda, atau dimanapun di dunia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Lítið forrit til að fylgjast með veðurskilyrðum og spám fyrir ákveðinn stað, eða í heiminum öllum.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Una semplice applicazione per controllare le condizioni meteorologiche della propria città o di qualsiasi altra località.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">あなたの街や、世界中の都市の現在の天候を確認することができる小さなアプリケーションです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Өз қалаңыз, немесе әлемнің басқа жерлері үшін ағымдағы ауа райы жағдайын көрсететін кішігірім қолданба.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">당신이 사는 도시를 비롯하여 전세계 모든 곳의 현재 날씨를 알게 해주는 작은 프로그램입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Maža programa, kuri jums leidžia stebėti orų sąlygas jūsų mieste arba bet kur pasaulyje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Maza lietotne, kas palīdz uzraudzīt pašreizējos laikapstākļus jūsu pilsētā vai jebkurā citā pasaules vietā.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Et lite program som lar deg overvåke værforholdene for din by eller hvor som helst i verden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een kleine toepassing waarmee u de actuele weersomstandigheden kunt volgen in uw woonplaats, of waar ook ter wereld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Una pichona aplicacion que vos permet de susvelhar las condicions metèo dins vòstra vila o ont que siá dins lo mond.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇੱਕ ਛੋਟੀ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ, ਜੋ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਸ਼ਹਿਰ ਜਾਂ ਸੰਸਾਰ ਵਿੱਚੋਂ ਹੋਰ ਥਾਵਾਂ ਲਈ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਮੌਸਮ ਦਾ ਧਿਆਨ ਰੱਖਣ ਲਈ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Mały program umożliwiający monitorowanie obecnych warunków pogodowych w miejscu zamieszkania lub w dowolnym miejscu na świecie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Uma pequena aplicação que lhe permite monitorizar as condições atmosféricas atuais da sua cidade, ou qualquer outro local no mundo, e aceder a previsões atualizadas, até 7 dias, disponibilizadas por vários serviços na Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Um pequeno aplicativo que permite a você monitorar as atuais condições meteorológicas da sua cidade, ou qualquer lugar do mundo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">O mică aplicație ce permite monitorizarea condițiilor meteorologice pentru orașul dumneavoastră, sau orice loc din lume.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Небольшое приложение, которое позволяет отслеживать текущее состояние погоды для вашего города или любой точки мира.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Malá aplikácia, ktorá vám umožňuje sledovať aktuálne počasie vo vašom meste, alebo kdekoľvek vo svete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program, ki omogoča nadzor trenutnih vremenskih pogojev za izbrana mesta, kjerkoli na svetu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Програмче које вам омогућава да надгледате тренутне временске прилике за ваш град, или било где у свету.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Programče koje vam omogućava da nadgledate trenutne vremenske prilike za vaš grad, ili bilo gde u svetu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ett litet program som låter dig hålla koll på aktuella väderförhållanden för din stad eller andra platser i världen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Обу ҳаво барномаи хурдест, ки барои назорат кардани шароити обу ҳаво барои шаҳри шумо ё ягон шаҳи ҷаҳон имкон медиҳад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมเล็กๆ ที่ช่วยคุณติดตามสภาพอากาศปัจจุบันของเมืองของคุณ หรือที่ใดๆ ในโลก</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Şehrinizin ya da dünyadaki herhangi bir yerin geçerli hava durumunu gözleyebileceğiniz ufak bir uygulama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Маленька програма, яка дозволяє стежити за поточними погодними умовами вашого міста або будь-де в світі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng nhỏ cho phép bạn theo dõi điều kiện thời tiết hiện tại ở thành phố của bạn, hay bất kỳ nơi nào khác trên thế giới.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">一个允许你监控所在城市或世界各地的当前天气状况的小应用</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">一個小型應用程式，允許你監控你的城市或是世界中任一地區目前的天氣狀況。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">一個小型應用程式，允許您監控您的城市或是世界中任一地區目前的天氣狀況。</p>
    <p>It provides access to detailed forecasts, up to 7 days, with hourly details for the current and next day, using various internet services.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">Proporciona acceso a pronosticos actualizaus, dica 7 días, con detalles cada hora ta o día actual y o siguient, usando quantos servicios d'Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">ই বিভিন্ন ইন্টাৰনেট সেৱাসমূহ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি বৰ্তমান আৰু পৰৱৰ্তী দিনৰ বাবে প্ৰতি ঘন্টা বিৱৰণসমূহৰ সৈতে, ৭ দিন লৈকে, বিৱৰিত আগজাননী প্ৰদান কৰে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Има възможност за подробни прогнози — до седмица напред, с почасово състояние за текущия и следващия дни. Ползва различни източници по Интернет.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Omogućava pristup detaljnijoj vremenskoj prognozi, 7 dana unaprijed, sa detaljima po satu za trenutni i sljedeći dan, koristeći različite internet usluge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">També podeu accedir a les previsions actualitzades de fins a 7 dies i per hores pel dia actual i l'endemà. Proporcionades per diversos serveis d'Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">També podeu accedir a les previsions actualitzades de fins a 7 dies i per hores per el dia actual i l'endemà. Proporcionades per diversos serveis d'Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Díky využití několika internetových služeb poskytuje podrobnou předpověď až na 7 dní, pro dnešek a zítřek s detaily po hodinách.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Det tilbyder adgang til detaljerede vejrudsigter, op til syv dage, med time-detaljer for i dag og i morgen ved at benytte forskellige internettjenester.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Bietet Zugang zu detaillierter Wettervorhersage über bis zu 7 Tage mit stündlichen Details für den laufenden und den folgenden Tag auf Basis mehrerer Internetdienste.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Παρέχει πρόσβαση σε λεπτομερείς προβλέψεις, έως και 7 ημέρες, με ωριαία στοιχεία για την τρέχουσα και την επόμενη μέρα, με τη χρήση διαφόρων υπηρεσιών διαδικτύου.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Proporciona acceso a pronósticos actualizados, hasta 7 días, con detalles cada hora para el día actual y el siguiente, usando varios servicios de Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Iragarpen xehatuak ikusteko aukera ematen du, 7 egun artekoak, ordukako xehetasunak ematen dituztenak uneko egunerako eta hurrengo egunerako, hainbat Interneteko zerbitzu erabiliz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">دسترسی به پیش‌بینی‌های دقیق را تا ۷ روز فراهم می‌کند. همراه با جزئیات روزانه برای امروز و روز بعد، با استفاده از تعدادی از سرویس‌های اینترنتی.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se tarjoaa eri verkkopalveluita käyttäen yksityiskohtaisen ennusteen seuraavan viikon ajalle sekä tuntikohtaiset tiedot kuluvalle ja seuraavalle päivälle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Elle permet d'accéder à des prévisions détaillées jusqu'à 7 jours, avec des détails horaires pour le jour actuel et le lendemain, en utilisant divers services Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Al furnìs acès a previsions in detai (fin a 7 dîs), cun detais oraris par vuê e pal prossim dì, doprant plui servizis internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Bheir e dhut ro-aithris mionaideach suas gu 7 làithean le fiosrachadh airson gach uair airson an diugh 's a-màireach le taic o chaochladh sheirbheisean eadar-lìn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Fornece acceso a predicións detalladas ate 7 días, con información por hora do día actual e seguinte, usando varios servizos de internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">הוא מספק גישה לתחזיות מפורטות, עד לשבוע ימים, פרטים לפי שעה ליום הנוכחי ולזה שלאחריו, באמצעות שרתי אינטרנט שונים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Részletes előrejelzésekhez biztosít hozzáférést 7 napos időtávra, valamint különféle internetes szolgáltatásokat felhasználva óránkénti részleteket nyújt az aktuális és a következő napra.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini memberikan akses ke ramalan cuaca terrinci, sampai dengan 7 hari, dengan rincian per jam bagi hari ini dan besok, memakai berbagai layanan internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Það veitir aðgang að nákvæmum veðurspám, allt upp í 7 daga fram í tímann, með upplýsingar á klukkustundar fresti fyrir næstu 2 daga; það styðst við ýmsar þjónustur á internetinu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Fornisce accesso a previsioni dettagliate (fino a sette giorni) con dettagli orari del giorno attuale e di quello successivo sfruttando molteplici servizi Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">さまざまなインターネットサービスを使用して詳細な天気予報を参照できます。週間天気予報や、当日と翌日の時間ごとの詳細な天気予報などが利用できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Ол интернеттің бірнеше көздері ұсынатын, 7 күнге дейін алға, ал ағымдағы және келесі күн үшін сағат бойынша ақпараты бар ауа райы болжамдарын қарауды мүмкін қылады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">여러 인터넷 서비스에서 일주일까지의 자세한 일기 예보를 가져와 알려드리며, 오늘과 내일 날씨는 시간별로도 알 수 있게 해드립니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ji leidžia matyti iki 7 dienų prognozę su valandų tikslumo informacija, teikiamą įvairių interneto tarnybų.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Tā sniedz piekļuvi detalizētām prognozēm līdz 7 dienām, ar detalizāciju līdz stundām aktuālajai un nākamajai dienai, ko sniedz dažādi interneta servisi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Gir tilgang til detaljerte værmeldinger opp til syv dager med detaljer time for time for i dag og i morgen. Bruker forskjellige tjenester på internett.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U krijgt gedetailleerde weersverwachtingen, tot aan 7 dagen vooruit, met elk uur nieuwe informatie voor de huidige en volgende dag, geleverd door diverse internetdiensten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Permet d'accedir a de previsions detalhadas fins a 7 jorns, amb de detalhs oraris pel jorn actual e l'endeman, en utilizant divèrses servicis Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇਹ ਵੱਖ-ਵੱਖ ਇੰਟਰਨੈੱਟ ਸੇਵਾਵਾਂ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਕੇ 7 ਦਿਨਾਂ ਤੱਕ ਦੀ ਵੇਰਵੇ ਸਮੇਤ ਭਵਿੱਖਬਾਣੀ ਦਿੰਦੀ ਹੈ, ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ ਅੱਜ ਅਤੇ ਭਲਕ ਲਈ ਘੰਟਿਆਂ ਦੇ ਮੁਤਾਬਕ ਵੇਰਵਾ ਵੀ ਮੌਜੂਦ ਰਹਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zapewnia dostęp do dokładnych prognoz na 7 dni ze szczegółami na każdą godzinę w dniu bieżącym oraz następnym, korzystając z różnych serwisów internetowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Fornece acesso a previsões detalhadas até 7 dias, com detalhes horários para o dia atual e seguinte, usando vários serviços da Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Fornece acesso a previsões de tempo detalhadas, de até 7 dias, com detalhes de hora em hora para o dia atual e para o próximo, usando vários serviços da internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Oferă acces la prognoze meteo detaliate, până la 7 zile, cu detalii orare pentru ziua în curs și următoarea, folosing diferite servicii online.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Оно также предоставляет доступ к подробному прогнозу погоды (до 7 дней) от различных Интернет-служб.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Poskytuje prístup k podrobnej predpovedi až na 7 dní s hodinovými podrobnosťami pre aktuálny a nasledujúci deň prostredníctvom rozličných internetových služieb.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Omogoča prikaz podrobne vremenske napovedi različnih spletnih mest do 7 dni, z urno razdelitvijo poteka za en dan naprej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Обезбеђује приступ опширним временским прогнозама, до 7 дана, са једночасовним појединостима за текући и наредни дан, користећи разне интернет услуге.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Obezbeđuje pristup opširnim vremenskim prognozama, do 7 dana, sa jednočasovnim pojedinostima za tekući i naredni dan, koristeći razne internet usluge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det tillhandahåller detaljerade prognoser sju dagar framåt med detaljerad information per timme för aktuell och nästkommande dag, från diverse internettjänster.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Он пешгӯии обу ҳавои ботафсилро бо тафсилоти ҳар соата барои рӯзи ҷорӣ ва навбатӣ, ба воситаи хидматҳои интернетии гуногун, барои 7 рӯз таъмин менамояд.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">คุณจะสามารถเข้าถึงข้อมูลพยากรณ์อากาศ 7 วันข้างหน้า พร้อมรายละเอียดเป็นรายชั่วโมงสำหรับวันปัจจุบันและวันถัดไป จากบริการต่างๆ หลายแหล่งในอินเทอร์เน็ต</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Çeşitli internet hizmetleri kullanarak 7 güne kadar detaylı tahminlerle birlikte şimdiki ve sonraki gün için saatlik detaylara erişmeyi sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма надає доступ до детального прогнозу, до семи днів, з погодинними подробицями для поточного і наступного дня, використовуючи різні служби в інтернеті.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Nó cung cấp dự báo thời tiết chi tiết đến bảy ngày, chi tiết đến từng giờ cho hôm nay và ngày kế tiếp, sử dụng các dịch vụ internet khác nhau</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">它使用各种不同的网络服务，提供非常具体的 7 天的天气预报，包括当天和第二天的每个小时的具体天气。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">它提供了詳細的天氣預報，最多達 7 天，有每小時針對目前與明天的詳細資料，使用各種互聯網服務提供。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">它提供了詳細的天氣預報，最多達 7 天，有每小時針對目前與明天的詳細資料，使用各種網際網路服務提供。</p>
    <p>It also optionally integrates with the GNOME Shell, allowing you see the current conditions of the most recently searched cities by just typing its name in the Activities Overview.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">Tamién s'integra opcionalment con GNOME Shell, permitindo-le veyer as condicions actuals de qualsiquier ciudat buscada recientment simplament escribindo o suyo nombre en a vista d'actividatz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">ই লগতে বিকল্পভাৱে GNOME শ্বেলৰ সৈতে অনুকলন কৰে, যাৰ বাবে আপুনি কাৰ্য্যসমূহ অভাৰভিউত এটা আটাইতকৈ শেহতীয়াভাৱে সন্ধান কৰা নগৰসমূহৰ কেৱল নাম টাইপ কৰি তাৰ বৰ্তমান অৱস্থা চাব পাৰিব।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Може да се интегрира с обвивката на GNOME — GNOME Shell, което ви дава възможност да видите текущите метеорологични условия в скоро търсените градове като просто напишете името им в прегледа на дейностите.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Također opcionalno integrisano sa GNOME Shell-om, dopušta pregled trenutnih uslova nedavno pretraživanih gradova upisivajem njihovih imena u pregled aktivnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Opcionalment també es pot integrar amb el GNOME Shell de manera que vegeu les condicions actuals de les últimes ciutats que hagueu cercat teclejant el seu nom al resum d'activitats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Opcionalment també es pot integrar amb el GNOME Shell de manera que vegeu les condicions actuals de les últimes ciutats que hagueu cercat teclejant el seu nom al resum d'activitats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Umí se integrovat do prostředím GNOME Shell, takže si můžete zobrazit aktuální počasí v nedávno vyhledaných městech napsaním jejich názvu v přehledu činností.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Der er også valgfri integration med GNOME Shell, som tillader dig at se de nuværende forhold i de senest søgte byer, blot ved at indtaste byens navn i Aktivitets-oversigten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Lässt sich auf Wunsch in die GNOME-Shell einbinden, so dass Sie sich über das aktuelle Wetter jeder eingegebenen Stadt informieren können, indem Sie den Ortsnamen in die Aktivitätenübersicht eingeben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Επίσης ενσωματώνεται προαιρετικά με το GNOME Shell, επιτρέποντάς σας να δείτε τις τρέχουσες συνθήκες οποιασδήποτε πόλης έχει ρυθμιστεί απλά πληκτρολογώντας το όνομα στην επισκόπιση Δραστηριότητες.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">También se integra opcionalmente con GNOME Shell, permitiéndole ver las condiciones actuales de cualquier ciudad buscada recientemente simplemente escribiendo su nombre en la vista de actividades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Aukeran GNOME Shell-ekin bateragarria da, azken aldian bilatutako herrien (hauen izenak jardueren ikuspegian idatziz) uneko baldintzak ikusteko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">همچنین به‌طور اختیاری قابلیت یکپارچگی با پوسته‌گنوم را نیز دارد، به شما اجازه می‌دهد تا وضعیت فعلی برای آخرین شهرهای جست‌وجو شده را فقط با تایپ نام آن در نمای‌کلی فعالیت‌ها ببینید.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se myös mukautuu Gnome Shelliin, jolloin viimeksi tarkasteltujen sijaintien säätiedot ovat nähtävissä Shellin yleisnäkymässä kirjoittamalla paikkakunnan nimen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Elle peut également s'intégrer à GNOME Shell, permettant de voir les conditions actuelles de n'importe quelle ville configurée en tapant simplement son nom dans la vue d'ensemble des activités.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Volint ancje a si integre cun GNOME Shell, permetint di viodi lis condizions meteo atuâi des citâts plui cirudis di resint, dome scrivint il lôr non inte panoramiche "Ativitâts".</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Gabhaidh amalachadh leis an t-slige GNOME ma thogras tu 's mar sin airson nam bailtean a lorg thu o chionn goirid, cha leig thu leas ach ainm baile a sgrìobhadh ann am foir-shealladh nan gnìomhachdan ach am faic thu an aimsir airson a' bhaile ud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Tamén se integra con GNOME Shell o que lle permite ver as condicións meteorolóxicas actuais das cidades máis buscadas recentemente escribindo o seu nome na Vista de actividades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">כמו כן הוא ניתן לשילוב עם מעטפת GNOME, המאפשר לך לראות את תנאי מזג האוויר של רוב הערים שחיפשת לאחרונה, רק בהקלדת שם בסקירת פעילויות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Ezen felül opcionálisan beépül a GNOME parancsértelmezőbe, lehetővé téve a leggyakrabban keresett városok aktuális időjárásának megtekintését azok neveinek begépelésével a tevékenységek áttekintőjébe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini secara opsional juga terintegrasi dengan GNOME Shell, memungkinkan Anda melihat kondisi saat ini dari kota yang baru-baru ini dicari hanya dengan mengetikkan namanya dalam Ringkasan Aktivitas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Hægt er að fella það inn í GNOME Skelina, þannig að þú getur séð veðurskilyrði í þeim borgum sem síðast hefur verið leitað að með því einu að slá nafn þeirra inn í aðgerðayfirlitið.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Può anche essere integrata, opzionalmente, con GNOME Shell, consentendo di visualizzare le condizioni correnti delle città visitate recentemente digitandone il nome nella panoramica «Attività».</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">GNOME Shell と統合することができ、アクティビティ画面で都市名を入力することで、よく調べる都市の現在の天候を参照することができます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Сонымен қатар, оның GNOME Shell ішіне интеграциясы бар, белсенділік көрінісінде жақында ізделген қалалар үшін ауа райы болжамын көрсете алады, ол үшін қала атын енгізу керек.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">그놈 쉘에 붙어 자주 찾은 도시의 이름을 현재 활동에 치는 것만으로 현재 날씨를 보여드릴 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ji taip pat integruojasi su GNOME Shell, leisdama matyti orų sąlygas paskutiniuose ieškotuose miestuose tiesiog įvedant jų pavadinimus veiklų apžvalgoje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">To var arī integrēt ar GNOME čaulu, ļaujot redzēt apstākļus nesen meklētajās pilsētās, ievadot to nosaukumus aktivitāšu pārskatā.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Integrerer også med GNOME skallet, og lar deg se tilstanden i de mest brukte byene ved å søke etter navnet i aktivitetsoversikten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het integreert ook desgewenst met de Gnome Shell en biedt u de mogelijkheid de huidige weersomstandigheden te zien van de meest recent gezochte steden door gewoon de naam ervan in te geven in het activiteitenoverzicht.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Tanben, se pòt integrar a GNOME Shell, e permetre de veire las condicions actualas de quins vila configurada que siá en picant simplament son nom dins la vista d'ensemble de las activitats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇਹ ਚੋਣਵੇਂ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਗਨੋਮ ਸ਼ੈੱਲ ਨਾਲ ਵੀ ਜੁੜਿਆ ਹੋਈ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸਰਗਰਮੀ ਸੰਖੇਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਕਿਸੇ ਲੱਭੇ ਗਏ ਸ਼ਹਿਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਕੇਵਲ ਨਾਂ ਲਿਖ ਕੇ ਹੀ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਹਾਲਤ ਨੂੰ ਵੇਖਣ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program można również zintegrować z powłoką GNOME, co umożliwia dostęp do obecnych warunków pogodowych w ostatnio wyszukiwanych miastach poprzez wpisanie ich nazw w ekranie podglądu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Também se integra, opcionalmente, com a shell do GNOME, permitindo-lhe ver as condições atuais das cidades mais recentemente procuradas, simplesmente digitando o seu nome na vista de atividades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Ele também integra-se, de forma opcional, com o GNOME Shell, permitindo que você veja as condições atuais das cidades mais pesquisadas recentemente, bastando digitar o nome dela no Panorama de Atividades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">De asemenea, opțional, se poate integra în GNOME Shell, și vă permite să observați condițiile meteo curente pentru oricare oraș configurat prin simpla introducere a numelui în caseta de căutare din panorama Activități.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение также может интегрироваться в GNOME Shell: можно посмотреть погоду последних искомых городов (название города вводится в режиме обзора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Tiež je dostupná voliteľná integrácia so Shellom prostredia GNOME, ktorá vám umožní vidieť aktuálne podmienky naposledy hľadaných miest zadaním ich názvov v prehľade aktivít.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Izbirno se program vključuje tudi v okolje Lupine GNOME in omogoča pregled trenutnega vremena v izbranih oziroma iskanih mestih.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Такође се може објединити са Гномовом шкољком, омогућавајући вам да видите тренутне услове последњих тражених градова једноставним куцањем њихових имена у прегледу активности.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Takođe se može objediniti sa Gnomovom školjkom, omogućavajući vam da vidite trenutne uslove poslednjih traženih gradova jednostavnim kucanjem njihovih imena u pregledu aktivnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det integrerar också valfritt med GNOME-skalet, vilket gör det möjligt för dig att se aktuella förhållanden för de senast eftersökta städerna genom att bara skriva dess namn i Aktivitetsöversikten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">นอกจากนี้ยังสามารถเชื่อมรวมกับเชลล์ GNOME ทำให้คุณเห็นสภาพปัจจุบันของเมืองที่ค้นหาล่าสุด โดยเพียงพิมพ์ชื่อเมืองในภาพรวมกิจกรรม</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">İsteğe bağlı olarak GNOME Shell ile birleşir, Etkinlikler Genel Görünümüne son aranan şehirlerin sadece ismini girerek geçerli hava durumlarını görmenizi sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Також необов'язково вбудовується в GNOME Shell, дозволяючи бачити поточні погодні умови найнедавніших міст просто ввівши його назву в огляді діяльності.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Nó cũng được tích hợp cùng Hệ vỏ GNOME, cho phép bạn xem tình hình hiện tại của các thành phố mới tìm bằng cách gõ tên vào "Tổng quan hoạt động"</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">它也集成到了 GNOME Shell，允许你通过在活动概览中输入名字来查看最近搜索的城市的当前状况。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">它也可以選擇性與 GNOME Shell 整合，允許你在活動概覽中輸入名稱就可以搜尋最近尋找過的城市並查看它目前的天氣狀況。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">它也可以選擇性與 GNOME Shell 整合，允許您在活動概覽中輸入名稱就可以搜尋最近尋找過的城市並查看它目前的天氣狀況。</p>
  </description>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1500" height="1130">https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-weather/plain/misc/screenshots/city-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1500" height="1130">https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-weather/plain/misc/screenshots/world-popover.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Weather</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=gnome-weather</url>
  <updatecontact>gcampagna_at_src.gnome.org</updatecontact>
  <translation type="gettext">org.gnome.Weather</translation>
</component>