<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
  <id type="desktop">org.gnome.Books.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Books</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الكتب</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Книги</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Knjige</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Llibres</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Knihy</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Bøger</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Bücher</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Βιβλία</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Books</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Libroj</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Libros</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Liburuak</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">کتاب‌ها</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kirjat</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Livres</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Libris</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Leabhair</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Libros</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">ספרים</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Könyvek</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Buku</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Rafbækur</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Libri</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">ブック</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Кітаптар</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">책</name>
  <name xml:lang="ln">Buku</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Knygos</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Grāmatas</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Bøker</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Boeken</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Libres</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਕਿਤਾਬਾਂ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Książki</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Livros</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Livros</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Cărți</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Книги</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Knihy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Knjige</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Књиге</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Knjige</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Böcker</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">หนังสือ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kitaplar</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Книги</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Sách</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">图书</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">書籍</name>
  <summary>An e-book manager application for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تطبيق إدارة الكتب الرقمية لجنوم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Програма за управление на е-книги в GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Program upravljitelj elektronskim knjigama za GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una aplicació per gestionar llibres electrònics al GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Aplikace pro správu elektronických knih v GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Et program til håndtering af e-bøger i GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Eine Anwendung zur E-Bücher-Verwaltung für GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εφαρμογή διαχείρισης ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων του GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">An e-book manager application for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Retlibro-administrila aplikaĵo por GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una aplicación para gestionar libros electrónicos para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Liburu elektronikoak kudeatzeko GNOMEren aplikazio bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">یک برنامه مدیریت کتاب‌های الکترونیکی برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kirjojen hallintasovellus Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une application de gestion des livres numériques pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Une aplicazion GNOME par ministrâ e-book</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ga">Feidhmchlár bhainisteoireacht r-leabhar do GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Un aplicativo para xestionar libros dixitais para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">יישום לניהול ספרים אלקטרוניים עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Egy e-könyv kezelő alkalmazás a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Aplikasi manajer e-book bagi GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Rafbókaforrit fyrir GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Una applicazione GNOME per gestire e-book</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">GNOME の電子書籍管理アプリケーション</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">GNOME үшін электрондық кітаптарды басқару қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그놈용 전자책 관리 프로그램</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ln">Esaleli ya koyangela ba buku nimeriki pona GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">El. knygų tvarkymo programa GNOME aplinkai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">E-grāmatu pārvaldības lietotne GNOME vidē</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Et program for å håndtere e-bøker for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een Gnome-toepassing voor e-boekbeheer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Una aplicacion de gestion dels libres numerics per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਲਈ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program do zarządzania e-bookami dla środowiska GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma aplicação de gestão de e-books para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Um aplicativo para gerenciamento de e-book para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Un gestionar de cărți electronice pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Приложение для управления электронными книгами в GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Aplikácia na správu elektronických kníh pre GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Program za upravljanje z elektronskimi knjigami za namizje GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Гномов програм за управљање електронским књигама</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomov program za upravljanje elektronskim knjigama</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett program för hantering av e-böcker för GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมจัดการอีบุ๊กสำหรับ GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">GNOME için e-kitap yönetici uygulaması</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Організатор електронних книг для GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng quản lý sách điện tử dành cho môi trường GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 下的一款电子书管理应用程序</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 的電子書管理員應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>A simple application to access and organize your e-books on GNOME. It is meant to be a simple and elegant replacement for using a file manager to deal with e-books.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تطبيق بسيط للوصول إلى الكتب الرقمية و تنظيمها و مشاركتها في جنوم. صُمم ليكون بديلا بسيطًا و رائعًا عن مدير الملفات للتعامل مع الكتب الرقمية.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Опростено приложение за достъп, организиране и споделяне на е-книгите в GNOME. Предназначено е да бъде олекотен и елегантен заместник на файловия мениджър при работа с е-документи.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Jednostavan program za pristup i organizacijuvaših elektronskih knjiga na GNOME.Namijenjeno je da bude jednostavna i elegantna zamjena za korištenje upravitelja datoteka za rad sa elektronskim knjigama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Un programa simple per accedir i organitzar els llibres electrònics al GNOME. Està pensat per a ser un substitut simple i elegant d'un gestor de fitxers per als llibres electrònics.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Jednoduchá aplikace, kterou můžete používat pro přístup ke svým elektronickým knihám v GNOME a jejich roztřídění. Je zamýšlena jako snadná a elegantní náhrada za používání správce souborů k zacházení s e-knihami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Et simpelt program til at tilgå og organisere dine e-bøger i GNOME. Det er påtænkt at være en simpel og elegant erstatning for at bruge et filhåndteringsprogram til at håndtere e-bøger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Eine einfache Anwendung, um Ihre E-Bücher in GNOME zu betrachten und zu organisieren. Mit dieser Anwendung soll ein einfacher und eleganter Ersatz für eine Dateiverwaltung bereitgestellt werden, um mit E-Büchern zu arbeiten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μια απλή εφαρμογή για να έχετε πρόσβαση, να οργανώσετε τα ηλεκτρονικά σας βιβλία στο GNOME. Προορίζεται να είναι απλή και κομψή με σκοπό να αντικαταστήσει την διαχείριση των ηλεκτρονικών σας βιβλίων από τον διαχειριστή αρχείων.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">A simple application to access and organise your e-books on GNOME. It is meant to be a simple and elegant replacement for using a file manager to deal with e-books.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Una sencilla aplicación para acceder y organizar sus libros electrónicos en GNOME. Está pensada para ser un reemplazo sencillo elegante del uso de un gestor de archivos para gestionar sus libros electrónicos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Zure liburu elektronikoa GNOMEn atzitu eta antolatzeko aplikazio xume bat: hau da, liburu elektronikoekin aritzeko fitxategi-kudeatzaile baten ordezko xume eta dotore bat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">یک برنامه ساده برای دسترسی و مدیریت کتاب‌های الکترونیکی در گنوم. این برنامه سعی می‌کند نسبت به یک برنامه مدیریت پرونده ساده‌تر و بهتر برای کتاب‌های الکترونیکی عمل کند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Yksinkertainen Gnome-sovellus kirjojen käyttöä, organisointia ja jakamista varten. Sen on tarkoitus korvata tiedostonhallinta kirjoihin liittyvässä käytössä. Saumattoman pilvi-integraation tarjoaa Gnomen verkkotilit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Une application simple pour accéder à vos livres numériques et les organiser dans GNOME. Son but est d'être une alternative simple et élégante à l'utilisation d'un gestionnaire de fichiers pour traiter les livres numériques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Une semplice aplicazion par acedi, organizâ e condividi su GNOME i propris e-book. E je pensade par jessi une alternative semplice e elegant a un file manager te gjestion dai documents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Un aplicativo sinxelo para acceder, organizar e compartir os seus documentos en GNOME. Está pensado para que sexa unha alternativa simple e elegante ao uso do explorador de ficheiros para xestionar os seus libros dixitais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יישום פשוט לגישה ולארגון הספרים האלקטרוניים שלך על GNOME. היישום משמש חלופה פשוטה ואלגנטית למנהל קבצים לצורך טיפול בספרים אלקטרוניים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Egyszerű alkalmazás e-könyvek eléréséhez és rendszerezéséhez GNOME alatt. A fájlkezelő e-könyvek kezelésére való használatának egyszerű és elegáns helyettesítésére tervezték.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Aplikasi sederhana untuk mengakses dan mengelola e-book Anda pada GNOME. Ini dimaksudkan sebagai pengganti yang sederhana dan elegan dari manajer berkas untuk berurusan dengan e-book.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Una semplice applicazione per accedere, organizzare e condividere su GNOME i propri e-book. È pensata per essere un'alternativa semplice ed elegante all'utilizzo di un file manager nella gestione dei documenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">GNOME 上で電子書籍を楽しんだり、管理できるシンプルなアプリケーションです。シンプルさとエレガントさを特長としており、電子書籍を楽しむためにファイルマネージャーを使う必要はありません。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">GNOME ішінде электрондық кітаптарыңызға қатынау және оларды реттеу үшін арналған қарапайым қолданба. Ол эл. кітаптармен жұмысы үшін файлдар басқарушысын алмастыратын қарапайым әрі элегантты шешім ретінде ұсынылады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">그놈에서 전자책을 살펴보고 관리하는 간단한 프로그램입니다. 전자책을 다루려 파일 관리자를 사용할 때 간단하고 매력적인 대안 프로그램임을 의미합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ln">Esaleli ya mpamba pona koyingela na ba buku nimeriki na yo mpe koyangela  na GNOME. Ntina na ye ezali kozala boponi ya mpamba mpe ya kitoko na bosaleli moyangeli ya ba kasa pona kosala ba buku nimeriki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Paprasta programa GNOME aplinkai el. knygų pasiekimui. Ji siekia būti paprastu ir elegantišku failų tvarkytuvės pakaitalu darbui su el. knygomis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Vienkārša lietotne e-grāmatu piekļūšanai, organizēšanai un koplietošanai GNOME vidē. Tā ir paredzēta kā datņu pārvaldnieka aizvietotājs darbam ar e-grāmatām.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Et enkelt program for å aksessere, organisere dine e-bøker i GNOME. Ment å være en enkel og elegant erstatning for å håndtere e-bøker med en filhåndterer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een eenvoudige toepassing om uw documenten op Gnome te beheren. Het is bedoeld als eenvoudige en elegante vervanging van een bestandsbeheerprogramma om met e-boeken te werken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Una aplicacion simpla per accedir a vòstres libres numerics e los organizar dins GNOME. Sa tòca es d'èsser una alternativa simpla e eleganta a l'utilizacion d'un gestionari de fichièrs per tractar los libres numerics.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੀਆਂ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਵਰਤਣ ਤੇ ਉਹਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਸੌਖੀ ਜੇਹੀ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਫਾਇਲ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਨੂੰ ਸੌਖਾ ਤੇ ਸਧਾਰਨ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਤਿਆਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Prosty program umożliwiający czytanie i organizowanie e-booków w środowisku GNOME. Został on zaprojektowany jako prosty i elegancki interfejs do zarządzania e-bookami, zastępujący w tym celu menedżer plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Uma aplicação simples para aceder, organizar e partilhar os seus e-books no GNOME. Tem por objetivo ser uma forma simples e elegante de substituir a utilização de um gestor de ficheiros para gerir e-books.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Um aplicativo simples para acessar, organizar e compartilhar seus e-books no GNOME. Ele foi feito para servir como uma substituição simples e elegante de gerenciador de arquivos para lidar com e-books.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">O aplicație simplă care vă permite să accesați, organizați și să partajați cărțile electronice în mediul GNOME. Se dorește a fi un înlocuitor simplu și elegant pentru utilizarea unui gestionar de fișiere în lucrul cu cărțile electronice. Oferă integrare cloud perfectă prin Conturi Online GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Простое приложение для управления электронными книгами в GNOME. Это приложение предоставляет простую и элегантную замену файловому менеджеру при работе с электронными книгами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Jednoduchá aplikácia prostredia GNOME na prístup k vašim elektronickým knihám a ich organizáciu. Cieľom tejto aplikácie je jednoducho a elegantne nahradiť správcu súborov ako prehliadač e-kníh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Enosaven program za urejanje in izmenjavo elektronskih knjig na namizju GNOME. Zamišljen je kot enostavno orodje, ki naj bi nadomestilo uporabo upravljalnika datotek za take naloge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Једноставан програм за приступ и сређивање електронских књига на Гному. Замишљен је да буде једноставна и пригодна замена управника датотека за рад са електронским књигама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Jednostavan program za pristup i sređivanje elektronskih knjiga na Gnomu. Zamišljen je da bude jednostavna i prigodna zamena upravnika datoteka za rad sa elektronskim knjigama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ett enkelt program för att komma åt och organisera dina e-böcker i GNOME. Det är avsett att vara en enkel och elegant ersättare för att hantera e-böcker med en filhanterare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมอย่างง่ายสำหรับเข้าถึงและจัดระเบียบอีบุ๊กของคุณใน GNOME เป็นโปรแกรมเรียบหรูที่ใช้แทนโปรแกรมจัดการแฟ้มในการจัดการกับอีบุ๊ก</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">GNOME üzerinde belgelerinize erişmek, onları düzenlemek için basit bir uygulama. E-kitaplarınızı düzenlemek için dosya yöneticisinin yerini alabilecek basit ve şık bir çözüm olarak geliştirildi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Проста програма, щоб доступитись, упорядкувати ваші електронні книги в GNOME. Тобто це проста і витончена заміна файлового менеджера для роботи з електронними книгами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Đây là ứng dụng đơn giản để truy cập, tổ chức sách điện tử của bạn trên môi trường GNOME. Điều đó có nghĩa là nó phù hợp để thay thế cho bộ quản lý tập tin khi dùng với sách điện tử.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 下一款可访问、管理您的电子书的简洁应用。它的目标是成为一款替代文件管理器来处理电子书的优雅工具。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">簡單的應用程式，讓您可以在 GNOME 中存取與管理您的電子書。它希望能成為以檔案管理程式處理電子書的簡單優雅替代方案。</p>
    <p>It lets you:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يتيح لك:</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">ই আপোনাক অনুমতি দিয়ে:</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Праграма дазваляе:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Чрез него можете да:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bn_IN">অাপনাকে অনুমতি দেয়:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">To vam omogućuje :</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Us permet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Vos permet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Můžete v ní dělat následující věci:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Den lader dig:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Sie ermöglicht Ihnen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Σας επιτρέπει να:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">It lets you:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Le permite:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">See võimaldab sul:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Honakoak eskaintzen dizkizu:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">به شما اجازه می‌دهد:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Sen avulla voit:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Elle vous permet de :</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">A permet di:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ga">Ligeann sé duit:</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Permítelle:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">היישום מאפשר לך:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">आपको करने देता है:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Lehetővé teszi:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini memungkinkan Anda:</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Gerir þér kleift að:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Permette di:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">機能:</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Мүмкіндіктері:</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">ಇದು ನಿಮಗೆ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 프로그램에는 다음 기능이 있습니다:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ln">Ezo sunga yo pona:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ji jums leidžia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Tās jums ļauj:</p>
    <p xml:lang="mr">तुम्हाला खालील पुरवेल:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Det lar deg:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt hiermee:</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Vos permet de :</p>
    <p xml:lang="or">ଏହା ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦେଇଥାଏ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਲਈ ਹੈ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program umożliwia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Permite-lhe:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Ele permite que você:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Vă oferă posibilitatea să:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Позволяет:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Umožňuje vám:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Omogoča:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Омогућава вам да:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Omogućava vam da:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det låter dig:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ta">இதைக் கொண்டு நீங்கள் செய்யக்கூடியவை:</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">ఇది మిమ్మల్ని:</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ช่วยให้คุณ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Şunları yapmanıza olanak tanır:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма дозволяє:</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Nó giúp bạn:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">它允许您：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">它讓你可以：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">它讓您可以：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>View recent e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض الكتب الرقمية الحديثة</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Скорошни е-книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Pogledaj nedavne elektronske knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualitza els llibres electrònics recents</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zobrazit si nedávné e-knihy</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Vis seneste e-bøger</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kürzlich verwendete E-Bücher anzuzeigen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Προβολή πρόσφατων ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">View recent e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Rigardi pasintajn retlibrojn</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ver los libros recientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Ikusi azken liburu elek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">نمایش کتاب‌های الکترونیکی اخیر</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Katsella viimeisimpiä kirjoja</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Consulter les dernières parutions</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Viodi e-book resints</li>
      <li xml:lang="ga">Amharc ar r-leabhair le déanaí</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Ver os libros dixitais recentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">הצגת הספרים האלקטרוניים האחרונים</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Legutóbbi e-könyvek megtekintése</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tilik e-book baru-baru ini</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Skoða nýlegar rafbækur</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzare e-book recenti</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">最近読んだ電子書籍の表示</li>
      <li xml:lang="kk">Соңғы эл. кітаптарды қарау</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">최근 전자책 보기</li>
      <li xml:lang="ln">Tala ba buku nimeriki ya suka</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Rodyti nesenai naudotas el. knygas</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Skatīt nesenās e-grāmatas</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Vis nylige e-bøker</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Recente e-boeken bekijken</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Consultar las darrièras parucions</li>
      <li xml:lang="pa">ਤਾਜ਼ਾ ਈ-ਕਿਤਾਬਾਂ ਵੇਖੋ</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przeglądanie ostatnio używanych e-booków</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ver e-books recentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Ver e-books recentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Vedeți cărți electronice recente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">открывать последние электронные книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zobraziť nedávne e-knihy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Nedavne elektronske knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Погледате скорашње е-књиге</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Pogledate skorašnje e-knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visa senaste e-böcker</li>
      <li xml:lang="th">ดูอีบุ๊กล่าสุด</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yakın zamanda kullanılan e-kitapları görüntülemek</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Переглянути нещодавні книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Sách điện tử bạn mới dùng</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">查看最近的电子书</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">檢視最近使用的電子書</li>
      <li>Search through e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">البحث قي الكتب الرقمية</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Търсене в e-книгите</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Traži kroz elektronske knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerqueu als llibres</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Vyhledávat v e-knihách</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Søge gennem e-bøger</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">In E-Bücher zu suchen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αναζητήσετε σε ηλεκτρονικά βιβλία</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Search through e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Buscar en los libros electrónicos</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bilatu liburu elektronikoen artean</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">جست‌وجو بر اساس کتاب‌های الکترونیکی</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Etsiä kirjojen sisällöstä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Chercher parmi votre bibliothèque</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Cirî tai e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="ga">Cuardaigh r-leabhair</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Buscar entre os libros dixitais</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">חיפוש מבעד לספרים אלקטרוניים</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Keresés az e-könyvekben</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Cari di antara e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Leita í rafbókum</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Cercare tra gli e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">電子書籍の検索</li>
      <li xml:lang="kk">Эл. кітаптар ішінен іздеу</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">전자책 검색</li>
      <li xml:lang="ln">Luka nakati ya bibilyotèque</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Ieškokite el. knygose</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Meklēt e-grāmatās</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Søk i e-bøker</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">E-boeken doorzoeken</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Cercar demest vòstra bibliotèca</li>
      <li xml:lang="pa">ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਲੱਭੋ</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przeszukiwanie e-booków</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Pesquise através de e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Căutați prin documente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">выполнять поиск по электронными книгам</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vyhľadávať v e-knihách</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Iskanje v elektronskih knjigah</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Претражујете е-књиге</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Pretražujete e-knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Söka genom e-böcker</li>
      <li xml:lang="th">ค้นอีบุ๊ก</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">E-kitaplarda arama yapmak</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Шукати в книгах</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">Tìm trong sách điện tử</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">从电子书中搜索</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">搜尋電子書</li>
      <li>View e-books (PDF and comics) fullscreen</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض الكتب الرقمية بملء الشاشة</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Преглед на е-книгите (PDF и комикси) на цял екран</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualitzeu els llibres electrònics (PDF i còmics) a pantalla completa</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zobrazte si e-knihy (PDF a komiksy) přes celou obrazovku</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Vis e-bøger (PDF og tegneserier) i fuldskærm</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">E-Bücher (PDF und Comics) im Vollbildmodus anzuzeigen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Δείτε ηλεκτρονικά βιβλία (PDF και κόμικ) σε πλήρη οθόνη</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">View e-books (PDF and comics) fullscreen</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ver libros electrónicos (PDF y cómics) a pantalla completa</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Ikusi liburu elektronikoak (PDF eta komikiak) pantaila osoan</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">نمایش کتاب‌های الکترونیک (PDFها و کمیک‌ها) بصورت تمام‌صفحه</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Katsele sähköisiä kirjoja koko näytön tilassa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Lire les livres numériques (PDF et bandes dessinées) en plein écran</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Viôt a plen visôr e-book (PDF e fumets)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Ver os libros dixitais (PDF e bandas deseñadas) a pantalla completa</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">צפייה בספרים אלקטרוניים (PDF וקומיקס) במסך מלא</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">E-könyvek (PDF és képregények) megtekintése teljes képernyőn</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Lihat e-book (PDF dan komik) dalam layar penuh</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Skoða rafbækur (PDF og myndasögur) á heilskjá</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzare e-book (PDF e fumetti) a schermo intero</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">電子書籍 (PDF および Comic Book) のフルスクリーン表示</li>
      <li xml:lang="kk">Эл. кітаптарды (PDF және комикстер) толық экранда қарау</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">최대 화면으로 전자책(PDF, 만화) 보기</li>
      <li xml:lang="ln">Tanga ba buku nimeriki (PDF mpe bandi ya koyema) na emɔ́niselo mobimba</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Rodyti el. knygas (PDF ir komiksus) visame ekrane</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Skatīt e-grāmatas (PDF un komiksus) pilnekrāna režīmā</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Vis e-bøker (PDF og tegneserier) i fullskjerm</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">E-boeken (PDFs en strips) in volledig scherm bekijken</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Legir vòstres libres numerics (PDF e comics) en ecran complet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie e-booków (plików PDF i komiksów) w trybie pełnoekranowym</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ver e-books (PDF e banda desenhada) em ecrã completo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Veja e-books (PDF e revistas) em tela cheia</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр электронных книг (PDF и комиксы) в полноэкранном режиме</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prehliadať e-knihy (PDF a komiksy) v režime na celú obrazovku</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pokaži e-knjige (PDF in Stripi) v celozaslonskem načinu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Прегледате ПДФ књиге или стрипове преко целог екрана</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregledate PDF knjige ili stripove preko celog ekrana</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visa e-böcker (PDF och serier) i helskärmsläge</li>
      <li xml:lang="th">ดูอีบุ๊ก (PDF และการ์ตูน) แบบเต็มจอ</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">E-kitapları (PDF ve çizgi roman) tam ekran görüntülemek</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Переглядати книги (PDF або комікси) в повному екранні</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">全屏查看电子书（PDF 和漫画）</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">以全螢幕檢視電子書(PDF 與漫畫)</li>
      <li>Print e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">طباعة الكتب الرقمية</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Отпечатване на е-книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Štampaj elektronske knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Imprimeix els llibres electrònics</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Vytisknout e-knihy</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Udskrive e-bøger</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">E-Bücher zu drucken</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εκτυπώσετε ηλεκτρονικά βιβλία</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Print e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Presi retlibrojn</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Imprimir libros electrónicos</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Inprimatu liburu elektronikoak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fa">چاپ کتاب‌های الکترونیکی</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tulostaa kirjoja</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Imprimer les livres numériques</li>
      <li xml:lang="fur">Stampâ e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="ga">Priontáil r-leabhair</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Imprimir libros dixitais</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">הדפסת ספרים אלקטרוניים</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">E-könyvek nyomtatása</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Cetak e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="is">Prenta rafbækur</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Stampare e-book</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">電子書籍の印刷</li>
      <li xml:lang="kk">Эл. кітаптарды баспаға шығару</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">전자책 인쇄</li>
      <li xml:lang="ln">Bimisa ba buku nimeriki</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Spausdinti el. knygas</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Drukāt e-grāmatas</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Skriv ut e-bøker</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">E-boeken afdrukken</li>
      <li xml:lang="oc">Imprimir los libres numerics</li>
      <li xml:lang="pa">ਈ-ਬੁੱਕ ਛਾਪੋ</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Drukowanie e-booków</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Imprimir e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Imprima e-books</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Tipăriți cărți electronice</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">печатать электронные книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Tlačiť e-knihy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Natisni elektronske slike</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Штампате е-књиге</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Štampate e-knjige</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skriva ut e-böcker</li>
      <li xml:lang="th">จัดพิมพ์อีบุ๊ก</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">E-kitapları yazdırmak</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Надрукувати книги</li>
      <li xml:lang="vi">In sách điện tử</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">打印电子书</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">列印電子書</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Books</url>
  <updatecontact>debarshir_at_gnome.org</updatecontact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-documents/plain/data/screenshots/gnome-books-1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-documents/plain/data/screenshots/gnome-books-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-documents/plain/data/screenshots/gnome-books-3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</application>