<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Florian Müllner <fmuellner@gnome.org> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.Polari.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <name>Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Балаканина</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="tg">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">పొలారి</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Полари</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਪੋਲਾਰੀ</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">पोलारि</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">폴라리</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">پولاری</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Polario</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">Polari</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">پولاري</name>
  <summary>An Internet Relay Chat Client for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 的網際網路中繼聊天客戶端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">GNOME 的互聯網中繼聊天客戶端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 的 IRC 客户端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Клієнт ретрансляційної інтернетової балачки для GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">GNOME için İnternet Aktarmalı Sohbet İstemcisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">గ్నోమ్ కోసం ఒక ఇంటర్నెట్ రిలే క్లయింట్</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En IRC-chattklient för GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnom IRC klijent za ćaskanje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Гном ИРЦ клијент за ћаскање</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Odjemalec za IRC za GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Klient rozhovorov v službe IRC prostredia GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">IRC-клиент для GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Un client IRC pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Um cliente de bate-papo através da Internet (IRC) para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um cliente de Internet Relay Chat (IRC) para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Klient IRC dla środowiska GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਲਈ ਇੰਟਰਨੈੱਟ ਰਿਲੇਅ ਚੈਟ ਕਲਾਇਟ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Un client IRC per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een Internet Relay Chat-client voor Gnome</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">En Internet Relay Chat-klient for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">GNOME internetinio perdavimo pokalbių klientas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Internet Relay Chat klients GNOME videi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그놈 데스크톱 IRC 클라이언트</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">GNOME用インターネットリレーチャットクライアント</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un programma IRC per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Suatu Klien Internet Relay Chat untuk GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Interneten továbbított csevegés (IRC) kliens a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">לקוח IRC לסביבת GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Un cliente de Internet Relay Chat para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Un program IRC par GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un client de discussion relayée par Internet (IRC) pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">IRC-asiakassovellus Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">یک کارگیر بازپخش اینترنت (IRC) برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren IRCaren (Interneteko berriketa-zerbitzua) bezero bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un cliente de IRC para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">IRC-a kliento por GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">An Internet Relay Chat Client for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ένας πελάτης συνομιλίας μεταγωγής διαδικτύου για το GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein IRC-Client für GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">En Internet Relay Chat-klient for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Komunikační klient IRC pro GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Un client d'IRC per al GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un client d'IRC per al GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Internet Relay Chat klijent za GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">GNOME ৰ বাবে এটা ইন্টাৰনেট ৰিলে চেট ক্লাএন্ট</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">عميل المحادثة المنقولة بالإنترنت (IRC) لجنوم</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      A simple Internet Relay Chat (IRC) client that is designed to integrate
      seamlessly with GNOME; it features a simple and beautiful interface which
      allows you to focus on your conversations.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">簡易網際網路中繼聊天 (IRC) 客戶端，設計與 GNOME 無縫整合，欲以簡單、優美的介面，讓您專注於對話本身。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">一款简单的网络中继聊天（IRC）客户端，与 GNOME 无缝整合；它的特性是界面简洁美观，使您可以专注于聊天。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Простий клієнт IRC, який розроблено для стільничного середовища GNOME; він має простий і красивий інтерфейс, який дозволяє зосередитись на розмовах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">GNOME ile sorunsuz bir şekilde bütünleşecek şekilde tasarlanmış basit bir İnternet Aktarımlı Sohbet (IRC) istemcisi; konuşmalarınıza odaklanmanıza olanak veren basit ve güzel bir arayüze sahiptir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">గ్నోమ్ తోటి ఏకీకరించిన ఒక తేలికైన ఇంటర్నెట్ రిలే ఛాట్ (ఐఆర్‌సి) కక్షిదారు; ఇది తేలికైన మరియు అందమైన అంతరవర్తితో, మీ సంభాషణలపై దృష్టి కేంద్రీకరించేలా చేస్తూంది.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">En enkel klient för IRC (Internet Relay Chat) som är designad för att integrera sömlöst med GNOME. Den har ett vackert, enkelt gränssnitt som tillåter dig att fokusera dig på dina konversationer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Jednostavan klijent za ćaskanje prenešeno internetom (IRC) koji je napravljen sa namerom da bude neprimetno sjedinjen sa Gnomom. Odlikuje ga jednostavno i lepo sučelje koje vam omogućava da se usredsredite na vaše razgovore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Једноставан клијент за ћаскање пренешено интернетом (ИРЦ) који је направљен са намером да буде неприметно сједињен са Гномом. Одликује га једноставно и лепо сучеље које вам омогућава да се усредсредите на ваше разговоре.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Enostaven odjemalec IRC, zasnovan za okolje GNOME. Program ima enostaven in pregleden vmesnikč</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Jednoduchý program na komunikáciu cez IRC, ktorý je navrhnutý s cieľom úzkej integrácie do prostredia GNOME. Zahŕňa jednoduché a pohľadné rozhranie, ktoré vám umožní sústrediť sa na rozhovory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Простой IRC-клиент для GNOME; имеет простой и лаконичный интерфейс, который не отвлекает от бесед.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Un client simplu IRC (Internet Relay Chat) care oferă integrare perfectă cu mediul GNOME; beneficiază de o interfață simpatică ce vă permite să vă concentrați asupra conversațiilor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Um cliente simples de Internet Relay Chat (IRC) que é projetado para integrar de forma transparente com o GNOME. Ele possui uma interface simples e bonita que permite a você se concentrar em suas conversas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Um cliente simples de Internet Relay Chat (IRC), desenhado para se integrar com o GNOME; apresenta um interface simples e bonito que lhe permite focar-se nas suas conversas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Prosty klient sieci IRC (Internet Relay Chat) integrujący się ze środowiskiem GNOME. Zawiera on prosty i elegancki interfejs, umożliwiający skupienie się na rozmowach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇੱਕ ਸਧਾਰਨ ਇੰਟਰਨੈੱਟ ਰਿਲੇਅ ਚੈਟ (IRC) ਕਲਾਂਇਟ ਹੈ, ਗਨੋਮ ਨਾਲ ਡੂੰਘੇ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਜੁੜਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਦੇ ਫੀਚਰਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੌਖਾ ਅਤੇ ਖੂਬਸੂਰਤ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਕਿ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੀ ਗੱਲਬਾਤ ਉੱਤੇ ਕੇਂਦਰਿਤ ਰਹਿਣ ਲਈ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Un client IRC simple qu'es concebut per s'integrar perfèitament amb GNOME. Dispausa d'una interfàcia simpla e polida que permet de vos concentrer sus vòstras conversacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een eenvoudige Internet Relay Chat (IRC)-client gemaakt om zonder problemen met Gnome te integreren; het heeft een eenvoudige en mooie interface die ervoor zorgt dat u zich kunt concentreren op uw gesprekken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Paprastas internetinio perdavimo pokalbių (IRC) klientas, sukurtas sklandžiam integravimuisi su GNOME; jis turi paprastą ir gražią sąsają, kuri leidžia susitelkti ties pokalbiais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Vienkāršs Internet Relay Chat (IRC) klients, kas ir paredzēts integrēšanai ar GNOME. Tajā ir vienkārša un skaista saskarne, kas jums ļauj koncentrēties uz sarunām.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">간단한 IRC 클라이언트로 그놈 데스크톱과 매끄럽게 통합됩니다. 인터페이스가 간단하고 아름다워 대화에 집중할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">シンプルなインターネットリレーチャット(IRC)クライアントです。GNOME とシームレスに統合するように設計されています。会話に集中しやすいシンプルできれいなインターフェースを特長としています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Un client IRC (Internet Relay Chat) semplice e progettato per integrarsi con GNOME: un'interfaccia grafica esteticamente appagante che consente di concentrarsi sulle proprie conversazioni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Suatu klien Internet Relay Chat (IRC) sederhana yang dirancang untuk terintegrasi secara mulus dengan GNOME; ini memiliki fitur antar muka yang indah dan sederhana yang memungkinkan Anda fokus ke percakapan Anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Egyszerű IRC kliens, amelyet a GNOME-ba való tökéletes integrációra terveztek. Egyszerű és gyönyörű felülete van, amely lehetővé teszi a beszélgetésekre való koncentrálást.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">לקוח העברת שיחה באינטרנט (IRC) פשוט המשולב בצורה חלקה עם GNOME; הוא כולל ממשק פשוט ויפה המאפשר לך להתמקד בשיחות שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Un cliente simple de Internet Relay Chat (IRC) que está deseñado para integrarse perfectamente con GNOME. Conta cunha interface simple e bonita que lle permite enfocarse nas súas conversas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Un client IRC (Internet Relay Chat) sempliç e progjetât par integrâsi cun GNOME: une interface grafiche gratificant in estetiche che e permet di concentrâsi su lis propris conversazions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Un client IRC simple qui est conçu pour s'intégrer parfaitement avec GNOME. Il dispose d'une interface simple et belle qui permet de vous concentrer sur vos conversations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Yksinkertainen IRC-asiakassovellus Gnome-työpöydälle. Pelkistetty ja kaunis käyttöliittymä ei vie huomiota tärkeimmästä, eli keskusteluista.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">یک کارگیر ساده بازپخش اینترنت (IRC) که برای یکپارچگی با گنوم طراحی شده است؛ شامل یک واسط ساده و زیبا است که به شما اجازه می‌دهد تا بر روی گفت‌وگوهای خود تمرکز کنید.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">IRCrako (Interneteko berriketa-zerbitzua) bezero xume bat GNOMErekin bateratuta egoteko diseinatuta. Interfaze xume eta dotorea du zu berriketetan zentra zaitezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Un sencillo cliente de IRC diseñado para integrarse sin problemas con GNOME. Tiene una interfaz bonita y sencilla que le permite centrarse en sus conversaciones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">A simple Internet Relay Chat (IRC) client that is designed to integrate seamlessly with GNOME; it features a simple and beautiful interface which allows you to focus on your conversations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ένας απλός πελάτης μεταγωγής συνομιλίας διαδικτύου (IRC) που σχεδιάστηκε για αδιάλειπτη ενσωμάτωση με το GNOME· χαρακτηρίζεται από μια απλή και όμορφη διεπαφή που σας επιτρέπει να εστιάσετε στις συζητήσεις σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Ein einfaches Programm für Internet Relay Chats (IRC), das sich nahtlos in Gnome einbindet. Es bietet eine schlanke und schicke Oberfläche, damit Sie sich auf Ihre Unterhaltungen konzentrieren können.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">En simpel klient til Internet Relay Chat (IRC), som er designet til at integrere gnidningsfrit med GNOME; den har en simpel og smuk brugerflade, så du kan fokusere på dine samtaler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Jednoduchý klient IRC (Internet Relay Chat), který je navržen pro hladké začlenění do GNOME. Má jednoduché a pěkné uživatelské rozhraní, ve kterém se můžete plně věnovat diskuzím.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Un client d'IRC (Internet Relay Chat) senzill dissenyat per integrar-se sense problemes amb el GNOME. Inclou una interfície bonica i senzilla que vos permet centrar-vos en les vostres converses.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Un client d'IRC (Internet Relay Chat) senzill dissenyat per integrar-se sense problemes amb el GNOME. Inclou una interfície bonica i senzilla que us permet centrar-vos en les vostres converses.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Jednostavan Internet Relay Chat (IRC) klijent koji je dizajniran za neprimjetnu integraciju sa GNOME-om; Ima jednostavno i prekrasno sučelje koje vam omogućuje da se usredotočite na vaše razgovore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">এটা সাধাৰণ ইন্টাৰনেট ৰিলে চেট (IRC) ক্লাএন্ট যাক GNOME ৰ সৈতে সহজভাৱে অনুকলন কৰিবলে ৰূপাঙ্কণ কৰা হৈছে; ইয়াৰ এটা সাধাৰণ আৰু ধূনীয়া আন্তঃপৃষ্ঠ আছে যি আপোনাক আপোনাৰ কথোপকথনৰ ওপৰত মনোনিবেষ কৰায়।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">عميل بسيط للمحادثة المنقولة بالإنترنت (IRC) والمُصمم للتكامل بسلاسة مع جنوم.
يتميز التطبيق بالواجهة البسيطة والجذابة والتي تتيح لك التركيز على محادثاتك.</p>
    <p>
      You can use Polari to publicly chat with people in a channel, and to
      have private one-to-one conversations. Notifications make sure that
      you never miss an important message - for private conversations,
      they even allow you to reply instantly without switching back to the
      application!
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">您可以使用 Polari 與頻道中的人群公開討論，或是一對一的私人對話。通知功能能讓您不錯過重要訊息 - 私人談話甚至不必切換回應用程式就可以快速回覆！</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">你可以使用 Polari 在聊天室里与大家交谈，也可以进行一对一的私人谈话。通知推送确保你不会漏掉任何重要的消息 — 你甚至可以不切换回 Polari 即可及时回复私人信息！</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можете використовувати Polari для відкритих розмов з людьми на каналі й віч-на-віч. Сповіщення докладуться до того, щоб ви ніколи не пропускали повідомлення — для особистих розмов, вони навіть дозволять одразу відповісти без перемикання на саму програму. </p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Polari'yi, genele açık şekilde sohbet etmek ve diğer kişilerle özel konuşmalar gerçekleştirmek için kullanabilirsiniz. Bildirimler, önemli bir iletiyi asla kaçırmayacağınızdan emin olmanızı sağlar - ayrıca özel konuşmalarda, uygulamaya geri dönmeden anında cevap yazmanıza olanak tanır!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Du kan använda Polari för att chatta publikt med personer i en kanal, och ha privata enskilda samtal. Aviseringar garanterar dig att aldrig missa ett viktigt meddelande - för privata konversationer tillåter de dig till och med att svara omedelbart utan att växla tillbaka till programmet!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Polari možete koristiti za javno ćaskanje sa ljudima, na kanalu i za privatna ćaskanja. Sa obaveštenjima nikada nećete propustiti važnu poruku. Štaviše, za privatne razgovore je omogućeno odgovaranja iz samog obaveštenja bez potrebe za otvaranjem prozora programa!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Полари можете користити за јавно ћаскање са људима, на каналу и за приватна ћаскања. Са обавештењима никада нећете пропустити важну поруку. Штавише, за приватне разговоре је омогућено одговарања из самог обавештења без потребе за отварањем прозора програма!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Polari je program za klepetanje in sporočanje z zasebnimi sporočili. Opomniki obveščajo o pomembnih dogodkih in omogočajo hitro odgovarjanje preko obvestilnega polja programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">S použitím Polari môžete viesť verejné diskusie v skupinách alebo súkromné rozhovory s jedným partnerom. Vďaka oznámeniam nezmeškáte žiadne správy, dokonca môžete z lišty správ ihneď odpovedať na rozhovory bez toho, že by ste otvárali aplikačné okno.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение Polari используется для для публичного и приватного общения на чат-каналах. Благодаря уведомлениям вы никогда не пропустите важного сообщения, а для личных бесед можно ответить собеседнику прямо в уведомлении!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Puteți utiliza Polari atât pentru a conversa public cu persoane într-un canal de discuții cât și pentru conversații private unu-la-unu. Notificările asigură că nu ratați niciodată un mesaj important iar pentru discuțiile private, vă permite chiar să răspundeți instant, fără a fi nevoie să aduceți în prim plan fereastra aplicației!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Você pode usar o Polari para bater-papo publicamente com pessoas em um canal e para ter conversas particulares de um-para-um. As notificações garantem que você jamais se esqueça de uma mensagem importante - para conversas particulares, elas ainda permitem que você responda instantaneamente sem retornar ao aplicativo!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Pode usar o Polari para conversar publicamente com outros num canal e para ter conversas privadas. As notificações asseguram-se que não perde nenhuma mensagem importante - para conversas privadas, até pode responder imediatamente, sem ter de voltar à aplicação!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Można używać programu Polari do publicznych rozmów z innymi na kanale, a także do rozmów z tylko jedną osobą. Powiadomienia zapewniają, że żadna ważna wiadomość nie zostanie pominięta. Na prywatne wiadomości można odpowiadać od razu, bez przełączania się do programu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Podètz utilizar Polari per discutir publicament amb de monde dins de salons, e aver de conversacions privadas. Las notificacions vos asseguran que mancatz pas cap de messatge important - per las conversacions privadas, vos permeton quitament de respondre instantanèament sens tornar dins l'aplicacion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt Polari gebruiken om een publiek gesprek te voeren met mensen in een kanaal en om één-op-één-privégesprekken te voeren. Meldingen zorgen ervoor dat u nooit een belangrijk bericht zult missen - voor privégesprekken is het zelfs mogelijk om onmiddellijk te antwoorden zonder terug te keren naar de toepassing!</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Galite naudoti Polari viešiems pokalbiams kanale bei privatiems bendravimams. Pranešimai užtikrina, kad niekuomet nepraleistumėt svarbaus pranešimo - privatiems pokalbiams jie netgi leidžia tiesiogiai atsakyti nepersijungiant atgal į programą!</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Jūs varat izmantot Polari, lai publiski tērzētu ar cilvēkiem "istabās", vai arī privātās sarunās. Paziņojumi palīdz nepalaist garām svarīgus ziņojumus — privātās sarunās varat atbildēt uzreiz, nepārslēdzoties atpakaļ uz lietotni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">폴라리를 사용해 채널의 사람들과 대화할 수 있고, 개인적으로 일대일 대화를 할 수도 있습니다. 알림 기능을 이용해 중요한 메시지를 놓치지 않을 수 있습니다. 개인 대화의 경우에는 폴라리 프로그램으로 전환하지 않고 알림 창에서 즉시 대답을 할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Polariを使うとチャネル内の人々との公開チャットやプライベートな1対1の会話を行えます。重要なメッセージ (プライベートな会話など) を見逃さないように通知機能をサポートしており、しかもアプリケーションに画面を切り替えることなく、通知メッセージからすぐ返事することもできます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">È possibile usare Polari per chiacchierare con altre persone in un canale e avere conversazioni private. Le notifiche consentono di non perdere mai alcun messaggio importante: nelle conversazioni private è possibile rispondere immediatamente dalla notifica senza dover usare direttamente l'applicazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Anda dapat memakai Polari untuk mengobrol secara publik dengan orang-orang dalam suatu kanal, dan untuk menjalankan percakapan satu-ke-satu yang pribadi. Pemberitahuan memastikan bahwa Anda tak pernah melewatkan suatu pesan penting - untuk percakapan pribadi, bahkan dimungkinkan untuk menjawab seketika tanpa bertukar balik ke aplikasi!</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Polarit arra használhatja, hogy nyilvánosan csevegjen emberekkel egy közös csatornán, vagy privát csevegést folytasson másokkal. Az értesítések gondoskodnak arról, hogy sose maradjon le egyetlen fontos üzenetről sem - a privát csevegések esetén pedig arra is lehetősége van, hogy azonnal válaszoljon anélkül, hogy vissza kellene váltania az alkalmazáshoz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">ניתן להשתמש ב־Polari לשיחות ציבוריות עם אנשים בערוצים, וכן לשיחות פרטיות אחד על אחד. הודעות מוודאות שלעולם לא תפוספס אף הודעה חשובה - עבור שיחות פרטיות, ניתן אף להשיב מיידית מבלי לעבור חזרה ליישום!</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Pode usar Polari para conversar con xente de forma pública nunha canle e ter conversas un-a-un. As notificacións axudaranlle a non perder ningún mensaxe importante - para as conversas privadas, incluso lle permitirán contestar instantaneamente sen cambiar de aplicativo!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Al è pussibil doprâ Polari par cjacarâ cun altris personis intun canâl e vê conversazions privadis. Lis notifichis a permetin di no pierdi mai nissun messaç impuartant: tes conversazions privadis al è pussibil rispuindi subite, lì de notifiche, cence vê di doprâ par fuarce l'aplicazion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Vous pouvez utiliser Polari pour discuter publiquement avec des gens dans des salons, et avoir des conversations privées. Les notifications vous assurent que vous ne manquez aucun message important - pour les conversations privées, elles vous permettent même de répondre instantanément sans retourner dans l'application.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Voit käyttää Polaria julkiseen keskusteluun IRC-kanavilla tai kahdenkeskeiseen keskusteluun toisen käyttäjän kanssa. Ilmoitusten avulla tärkeät viestit eivät jää huomaamatta - voit jopa vastata kahdenkeskeisiin keskusteluihin suoraan ilmoituksen kautta vaihtamatta itse sovelluksen ikkunaan!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">شما می‌توانید از پولاری برای گپ عمومی در یک کانال استفاده کنید و یا گفت‌وگوهای خصوصی یک-به-یک داشته باشید. اعلان باعث می‌شوند تا هیچ‌وقت یک پیام مهم را - برای گفت‌وگوهای خصوصی - از دست ندهید، آنها حتی به شما اجازه می‌دهد تا بدون باز کردن برنامه به آنها پاسخ دهید!</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Polari erabil dezakezu jendearekin publikoki berriketan egiteko kanal batean, eta banan banako berriketa pribatuak edukitzeko. Jakinarazpenek mezu garrantzitsurik ez dituzula inoiz galduko ziurtatzen dute - berriketa pribatuentzako, gainera berehala erantzutea baimentzen dizute aplikaziora itzuli gabe. </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puede usar Polari para hablar públicamente con gente en un canal, y para tener conversaciones privadas. Las notificaciones aseguran que nunca perderá un mensaje importante; en conversaciones privadas, incluso le permiten contestar inmediatamente sin tener que volver a la aplicación.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">You can use Polari to publicly chat with people in a channel, and to have private one-to-one conversations. Notifications make sure that you never miss an important message - for private conversations, they even allow you to reply instantly without switching back to the application!</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μπορείτε να χρησιμοποιήσετε το Polari για να συνομιλήσετε δημόσια με ανθρώπους σε ένα κανάλι, και να έχετε ιδιωτικές συνομιλίες ένας προς έναν. Οι ειδοποιήσεις φροντίζουν ώστε να μην χάσετε ποτέ ένα σημαντικό μήνυμα - για ιδιωτικές συζητήσεις, σας επιτρέπουν επίσης να απαντήσετε απευθείας, χωρίς να κάνετε εναλλαγή στην εφαρμογή!</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Polari können Sie für Chats in öffentlichen Kanälen verwenden, es eignet sich jedoch auch für private Unterhaltungen. Benachrichtigungen sorgen dafür, dass Sie keine wichtige Nachricht mehr verpassen. Bei privaten Unterhaltungen können Sie sogar direkt antworten, ohne in das Anwendungsfenster wechseln zu müssen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Du kan bruge Polari til offentligt at chatte med folk i en kanal, samt til private samtaler. Påmindelser sikrer dig at du aldrig går glip af en vigtig meddelelse - for private samtaler, lader de dig endda svare omgående uden at du skal skifte tilbage til programmet!</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Polari můžete používat k veřejné diskuzi s lidmi na některém z kanálů nebo k soukromé konverzaci dvou lidí. Upozorňování zajistí, že nezmeškáte žádnou důležitou zprávu – u soukromých konverzací můžete dokonce ihned odpovědět, aniž byste se museli přepnout zpátky do aplikace Polari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Podeu utilitzar el Polari per parlar en públic en un canal i per tindre converses privades d'un a un. Les notificacions vos asseguren que no vos perdreu cap missatge important - per les converses privades fins i tot vos permeten respondre directament sense haver de canviar d'aplicació!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Podeu utilitzar el Polari per parlar en públic en un canal i per tenir converses privades d'un a un. Les notificacions us asseguren que no us perdreu cap missatge important - per les converses privades fins i tot us permeten respondre directament sense haver de canviar d'aplicació!</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Možete koristiti Polari i javno razgovarati s ljudima u kanal, i da imaju privatne jedan-na-jedan razgovore. Obavijesti osiguravaju da nikada nećete propustiti važnu poruku - za privatne razgovore, čak  vam oni i omogućuju  da odgovorite odmah, bez prelaska natrag na prijavu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">আপুনি Polari ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি এটা চেনেলৰ মানুহৰ সৈতে ৰাজহুৱাভাৱে চেট, আৰু ব্যক্তিগত কথোপকথনো কৰিব পাৰিব। অধিসূচনাসমূহে সুনিশ্চিত কৰে যে আপোনাৰ এটা গুৰুত্বপূৰ্ণ বাৰ্তা বাদ নাযায় - বিশেষকৈ ব্যক্তিগত কথোপকথনৰ বাবে, ই আপোনাক এপ্লিকেচনলৈ উভতি নহোৱাকৈ তৎক্ষনাত উত্তৰ দিয়াৰ সুবিধা দিয়ে।</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/polari/plain/data/appdata/polari-main.png?h=gnome-3-22</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/polari/plain/data/appdata/polari-user-list.png?h=gnome-3-22</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/polari/plain/data/appdata/polari-connection.png?h=gnome-3-22</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/polari/plain/data/appdata/polari-connection-properties.png?h=gnome-3-22</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Polari</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=polari</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <update_contact>fmuellner@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">polari</translation>
</component>
