<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Software Freedom Conservancy Inc. -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>shotwell.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <translation type="gettext">shotwell</translation>
  <name>Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">షాట్‌వెల్</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">ஷாட்வெல்</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Foto-bunar</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Фото-бунар</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਸ਼ੂਟਵੈੱਲ</name>
  <name xml:lang="or">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="mr">शॉटवेल</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഷോട്ട്‌‌വെല്‍</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">샷웰</name>
  <name xml:lang="kn">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">शॉटवेल</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="gu">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn_IN">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">Shotwell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">شُتْ‌وِل</name>
  <summary>Popular photo manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Popularni upravnik fotografija</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Популарни управник фотографија</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Obľúbený správca fotografií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Organizador popular de fotos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de fotografias popular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Popularny menedżer zdjęć</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Populārs fotogrāfiju pārvaldnieks</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">인기있는 사진 관리자</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Фотосуреттерді басқарудың әйгілі қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Népszerű fényképkezelő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מנהל תמונות פופולרי</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de fotos popular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Populäre Fotoverwaltung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Oblíbený správce fotografií</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Shotwell is an easy-to-use, fast photo organizer designed for the GNOME desktop.
      It allows you to import photos from your camera or disk, organize them by date and subject
      matter, even ratings.  It also offers basic photo editing, like crop, red-eye correction,
      color adjustments, and straighten.  Shotwell's non-destructive photo editor does not alter
      your master photos, making it easy to experiment and correct errors.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Foto-bunar je jednostavan za upotrebu, brz organizator fotografija osmišljen za Gnomovu radnu površ. Omogućava vam da uvezete fotografije sa foto-aparata ili diska, da ih razvrstate po datumu i predmetu, čak i prema oceni. Takođe nudi i osnovnu obradu slika, kao odsecanje, uklanjanje crvenih očiju, podešavanje boje, i ispravljanje. Foto-bunarov ne-uništavajući urednik fotografija ne menja vaše glavne fotografije, što olakšava eksperimentisanje i ispravljanje grešaka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Фото-бунар је једноставан за употребу, брз организатор фотографија осмишљен за Гномову радну површ. Омогућава вам да увезете фотографије са фото-апарата или диска, да их разврстате по датуму и предмету, чак и према оцени. Такође нуди и основну обраду слика, као одсецање, уклањање црвених очију, подешавање боје, и исправљање. Фото-бунаров не-уништавајући уредник фотографија не мења ваше главне фотографије, што олакшава експериментисање и исправљање грешака.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Shotwell é um organizador de fotos rápido e fácil de usar, projetado para o ambiente GNOME. Ele permite que você importe fotos de sua câmera ou sue disco, organize-os por data e assunto, e até mesmo avalie-as. Também oferece edição básica de fotos, como corte, correção de olho vermelho, ajuste de cor e correções. O editor de fotos não-destrutível do Shotwell não altera suas fotos mestres, tornando mais fácil experimentar e corrigir erros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Shotwell to łatwy w użyciu, szybki organizator zdjęć dla środowiska GNOME. Umożliwia on importowanie zdjęć z aparatu lub dysku, organizowanie ich według dat i tematyki, a nawet ocen. Oferuje on także podstawowe funkcje edycji zdjęć, takie jak kadrowanie, korekta efektu czerwonych oczu, dostosowanie kolorów i wyrównywanie. Niedestrukcyjny edytor zdjęć programu Shotwell nie zmienia głównych kopii zdjęć, znacznie ułatwiając eksperymentowanie i poprawianie błędów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Shotwell ir ātrs, viegli lietojams fotogrāfiju organizētājs, veidots GNOME darbvirsmai. Tas jums ļauj importēt fotogrāfijas no kameras uz disku, organizēt tās pēc datuma, tematikas vai par vērtējuma. Tas arī piedāvā vienkāršu fotogrāfiju rediģēšanu, piemēram, apcirst, novērst sarkano acu efektu, pielabot krāsas un iztaisnot bildi. Shotwell nedestruktīvā fotogrāfiju rediģēšana nemaina sākotnējo fotogrāfiju, kas jums ļauj eksperimentēt un labot kļūdas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">샷웰은 그놈 데스크톱에 맞춰 디자인 된 사용하기 쉬운 사진 정리 도구입니다. 카메라나 디스크에 있는 사진을 가져와 시간이나 주제에 따라 정리하고 사진을 잘라내거나 적목 현상을 제거하는 등의 기본적인 편집을 할 수 있습니다. 샷웰은 원본 사진 파일은 바꾸지 않기 때문에 편하게 사진의 오류를 수정하거나 실험할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Shotwell mudah digunakan, pengorganisasi foto yang didesain untuk desktop GNOME. Dapat digunakan untuk mengimpor foto dari kamera atau diska, organisasikan berdasarkan waktu dan subyek pokok, bahkan penilaian. Juga menawarkan penyuntingan foto dasar, seperti memotong, koreksi mata-merah, penyeimbang warna, pelurusan. Penyunting foto non-desktruktif Shotwell tidak mengubah foto asli Anda, sehingga aman untuk bereksperimen dan memperbaiki kesalahan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Shotwell egy könnyen használható, gyors fényképrendező a GNOME asztali környezethez. Segítségével fényképeket importálhat a fényképezőképéről vagy lemezekről, dátum, tárgy és értékelés szerint rendezheti őket. Alapvető fényképszerkesztést is biztosít, mint a vágás, vörös szem javítás, színállítás és egyenesítés. A Shotwell kárt nem okozó fényképszerkesztője nem módosítja az eredeti fényképeket, így könnyebbé teszi a kísérletezést és a hibák javítását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Shotwell הוא מנהל תמונות מהיר וקל לשימוש שעוצב עבור שולחן העבודה GNOME. הוא מאפשר לך לייבא תמונות מהמצלמה שלך לכונן הקשיח, לארגן אתם לפי תאריך, נושא ואפילו לפי דירוג. הוא גם מציע עריכת תמונות בסיסית, כמו חיתוך, תיקון עיניים אדומות, התאמת צבעים ויישור. עורך התמונות של Shotwell אינו הורס תמונות, הוא אינו משנה את התמונות המקוריות, מה שמקל על ביצוע ניסיונות ותיקון טעויות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Shotwell es un organizador de fotos fácil de usar, diseñado para el escritorio GNOME. Le permite importar fotos de su cámara o disco, organizarlas por fecha y asunto o por puntuación. También ofree edición básica, como recortar, eliminar ojos rojos, ajustes de color y enderezar. El editor no destructivo de Shotwell no altera las fotos originales, haciendo que sea más fácil experimentar y corregir errores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Shotwell ist eine einfach zu bedienende, schnelle Fotoverwaltung, die für die GNOME-Arbeitsumgebung entworfen wurde. Sie können Fotos von Ihrer Kamera oder einem Datenträger importieren, diese nach Datum oder Thematik ordnen und Bewertungen vergeben. Außerdem bietet Shotwell grundlegende Möglichkeiten zur Bildbearbeitung, wie beispielsweise Zuschneiden, Rote-Augen-Korrektur, Farbabgleich und Begradigen. Der zerstörungsfreie Fotoeditor verändert Ihre ursprünglichen Aufnahmen nicht, so dass Sie wesentlich freier damit experimentieren und Fehler korrigieren können.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Shotwell je rychlá a na obsluhu jednoduchá aplikace pro správu fotografií v uživatelském prostředí GNOME. Umožňuje import fotografií z fotoaparátu nebo disku, jejich roztřídění podle data a obsahu, a také hodnocení. Rovněž nabízí základní úpravy fotografií, jako je ořezání, oprava červených očí, vyladění barev a vyrovnání. Jedná se o nedestruktivní úpravy, což znamená, že editor nemění přímo hlavní fotografii, takže můžete snadno experimentovat a napravovat chyby.</p>
    <p>
      When ready, Shotwell can upload your photos to various web sites, such as Facebook, Flickr,
      Picasa (Google Plus), and more.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Kada ste spremni, Foto-bunar može da otpremi vaše fotografije na razne veb sajtove, kao što je Fejsbuk, Flikr, Pikasa (Gugl plus), i mnoge druge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Када сте спремни, Фото-бунар може да отпреми ваше фотографије на разне веб сајтове, као што је Фејсбук, Фликр, Пикаса (Гугл плус), и многе друге.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Quando estiver pronto, Shotwell pode enviar suas fotos para vários sites, tais como Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus) e mais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Quanto estiver pronto, o Shotwell pode enviar as suas fotografias para vários websites, tais como o Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus), entre outros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Po edycji, program Shotwell może wysłać zdjęcia do różnych serwisów internetowych, takich jak Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus) i wiele więcej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Shotwell var augšupielādēt jūsu fotogrāfijas dažādās tīmekļa vietnēs, piemēram, Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">준비가 되면 샷웰은 페이스북이나 플리커, 피카사(구글 플러스) 등의 웹 사이트에 사용자의 사진을 업로드할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ketika telah siap, Shotwell dapat mengunggah foto Anda ke berbagai situs web, seperti Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus), dan lain sebagainya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Ha készen áll, akkor a Shotwell képes feltölteni a képeit különböző weboldalakra, mint a Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus), és így tovább.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">בעת צפייה, Shotwell יכול להעלות את התמונות שלך למגוון של אתרי אינטרנט, כמו Facebook, Flickr, ‏Picasa ‏(Google Plus) ועוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Cuando esté preparado, Shotwell puede subir sus fotos a varios sitios web, tales como Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus) y más</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Wenn Shotwell eingerichtet ist, können Sie Ihre Fotos zu verschiedenen Webseiten hochladen, wie beispielsweise Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus) und weitere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Když máte vše připravené, může Shotwell nahrát vaše fotografie do různých webových služeb, jako je Facebook, Flickr, Picasa (Google Plus), Rajče a další.</p>
    <p>
      Shotwell supports JPEG, PNG, TIFF, and a variety of RAW file formats.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Foto-bunar podržava JPEG, PNG, TIFF i razne sirove zapise datoteka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Фото-бунар подржава ЈПЕГ, ПНГ, ТИФФ и разне сирове записе датотека.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Prehliadač Shotwell podporuje formáty JPEG, PNG, TIFF a množstvo súborov RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Shotwell oferece suporte a JPEG, PNG, TIFF e a uma variedade de formatos de arquivo RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Shotwell suporta JPEG, PNG, TIFF e vários formatos de ficheiros RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Shotwell obsługuje formaty JPEG, PNG, TIFF i wiele rodzajów plików RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Shotwell atbalsta JPEG, PNG, TIFF un dažādus jēlo datņu formātus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">샷웰은 JPEG, PNG, TIFF 그리고 다양한 RAW 파일 형식을 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Shotwell JPEG, PNG, TIFF және RAW файл пішімдерінің бірнеше түрлерін қолдайды.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Shotwell mendukung JPEG, PNG, TIFF, dan varietas berkas berformat RAW lainnya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Shotwell a JPEG, PNG, TIFF, valamint különböző nyers fájl formátumokat támogatja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Shotwell תומך ב־JPEG, PNG, TIFF ובתבניות קובץ RAW אחרות .</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Shotwell soporta JPEG, PNG, TIFF, y varios formatos de archivos RAW.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Shotwell unterstützt JPEG, PNG, TIFF und eine Reihe von RAW-Dateiformaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Shotwell podporuje souborové formáty JPEG, PNG, TIFF a různé varianty RAW.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Shotwell</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://shotwell-project.org/appdata/shotwell/harbor.png</image>
      <caption>
        <!-- Describe this screenshot in less than ~10 words -->
      </caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://shotwell-project.org/appdata/shotwell/import-300x155.png</image>
      <caption>
        <!-- Describe this screenshot in less than ~10 words -->
      </caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://shotwell-project.org/appdata/shotwell/organize-300x197.png</image>
      <caption>
        <!-- Describe this screenshot in less than ~10 words -->
      </caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://shotwell-project.org/appdata/shotwell/edit-300x247.png</image>
      <caption>
        <!-- Describe this screenshot in less than ~10 words -->
      </caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://shotwell-project.org/appdata/shotwell/publish-300x213.png</image>
      <caption>
        <!-- Describe this screenshot in less than ~10 words -->
      </caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>mail@jensge.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The Shotwell developers</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr@latin">Programeri Foto-bunara</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr">Програмери Фото-бунара</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Programiści projektu Shotwell</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Los desarrolladores de Shotwell</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Vývojáři aplikace Shotwell</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=shotwell</url>
  <!--GNOME Projects usually have no per-app donation page-->
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">http://shotwell-project.org/doc/html</url>
</component>
