<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id type="desktop">simple-scan.desktop</id>
  <metadata_licence>CC0-1.0</metadata_licence>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+ and CC-BY-SA-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">掃描易</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">簡易掃描</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">扫描易</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Quét đơn giản</name>
  <name xml:lang="uz">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Просте сканування</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">ئاددىي شويلىلاش</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Basit Tarama</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">సింపుల్ స్కాన్</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Enkel bildinläsning</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Обично скенирање</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Skanim i thjeshtë</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Enostavno optično branje</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché skenovanie</name>
  <name xml:lang="se">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="sd">سادو اسڪين</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Простое сканирование</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Scanare simplă</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Digitalização</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Digitalizador simples</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Proste skanowanie</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਸੌਖਾ ਸਕੈਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Aisina de numerizacion simpla</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Scannen</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="my">ရိုးရိုး Scan ဖတ်ခြင်း</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Pengimbas Ringkas</name>
  <name xml:lang="mhr">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Vienkārša skenēšana</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Paprastas skenavimas</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">심플 스캔</name>
  <name xml:lang="km">ស្កេន​ធម្មតា</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">シンプルスキャン</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Pemindai Ringkas</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Skeniranje dokumenata</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">סריקה פשוטה</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Escáner sinxelo</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Sganadh simplidh</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Outil de numérisation Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr_CA">Outil de numérisation Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kuvanluku</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Lihtne skannija</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Simpla skano</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Σάρωση</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Simpel skanning</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Jednoduché skenování</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Escaneig senzill</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Escaneig senzill</name>
  <name xml:lang="bo">པར་བཤུ་དཀྱུས་མ</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Опростено сканиране</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Simple Scan</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الماسحة الضوئية</name>
  <name xml:lang="am">ቀላል ማሰሻ</name>
  <name xml:lang="af">Eenvoudige Skandeer</name>
  <summary>Scan Documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">掃描文件</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">掃描文件</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">扫描文档</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Сканувати документи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">پۈتۈك شويلىلاش</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Belgeleri Tara</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">สแกนเอกสาร</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">పత్రాలు స్కాన్ చేయు</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Läs in dokument</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Скенирајте документе</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Skanoj Dokumentet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Optično preberite dokumente</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Skenuje dokumenty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sd">دستاويزات اسڪين ڪريو</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Сканирование документов</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Scanează documente</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Digitalizar documentos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Digitalizar documentos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Skanowanie dokumentów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਸਕੈਨ ਕੀਤੇ ਡੌਕੂਮੈਂਟ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Numerizar de documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Documenten scannen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Skann dokumenter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="my">Scan Documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Imbas Dokumen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Skenēt dokumentus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Skenuoti dokumentus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">스캔 문서</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="km">ស្កេន​ឯកសារ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">ドキュメントをスキャンします</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Acquisisci documenti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Pindai Dokumen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Dokumentumok szkennelése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Skenirajte dokumente</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">סריקת מסמכים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Escanear documentos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Sganaich sgrìobhainnean</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Numériser des documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr_CA">Numériser des documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Lue asiakirjoja kuvanlukijalta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Eskaneatu dokumentuak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Dokumentide skannimine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Escanear documentos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Skani dokumentojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Scan Documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Σάρωση εγγράφων</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Dokumente scannen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Skan dokumenter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Naskenovat dokumenty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Escanegeu documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Escanegeu documents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bo">ཡིག་གེ་པར་བཤུ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Сканиране на документи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">امسح المستندات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="am">ሰነድ ማሰሻ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="af">Skandeer dokumente</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      A really easy way to scan both documents and photos.
      You can crop out the bad parts of a photo and rotate it if it is the wrong way round.
      You can print your scans, export them to pdf, or save them in a range of image formats.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">您能輕易地掃描文件和相片。您可以裁剪相片的不良部分並將之旋轉至正確角度。您可以列印您的掃描檔，將掃描檔匯出成 pdf，或儲存為多種圖像檔案格式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">你能輕易地掃描文件和相片。你可以裁剪相片的不良部分並將之旋轉至正確角度。你可以列印你的掃描檔，將掃描檔匯出成 pdf，或儲存為多種圖像檔案格式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">一个非常简单的方法来同时扫描文档和照片。如果图片显示有误，您可以根据需要通过裁剪、旋转等方式调整照片。您也可以打印扫描件、导出 PDF 格式、或者保存为图片。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма для спрощення сканування документів та фотографій. За її допомогою ви зможете обрізати непотрібні частини сканованої фотографії та обернути її так, як потрібно. Передбачено можливості друку сканованих зображень, експортування даних до PDF та зберігання даних у файлах зображень різноманітних форматів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ett väldigt lätt sätt att skanna både dokument och foton. Du kan beskära bort dåliga delar av ett foto, och rotera det om det är felvänt. Du kan skriva ut det du skannat in, exportera till pdf, eller spara dem i ett brett utbud av bildformat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Једноставно решење за лако скенирање докумената и слика. Можете отсећи лоше делове слика и окренути скенирано. Можете штампати скенирано, одрадити извоз у ПДФ или сачувати скенирано у један од мноштва подржаних формата слика.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zelo enostaven način za optično branje tako dokumentov kot fotografij. Slabe dele fotografije lahko obrežete in fotografijo zavrtite, če je obrnjena. Prebrane dokumente lahko natisnete, izvozite v pdf ali shranite v eno od mnogih oblik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Skutočne jednoduchý spôsob ako oskenovať dokumenty aj fotografie. Môžete orezať nevhodné časti fotografie a otočiť ich podľa potreby. Vaše oskenované dokumenty môžete vytlačiť, exportovať ich do pdf, alebo ich uložiť v rôznych formátoch obrázkov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Наиболее простой способ сканирования документов и фотографий. Вы можете обрезать испорченные края снимков и повернуть их, если расположили неправильно. Вы можете распечатать сканированные материалы, экспортировать их в PDF или изображения ряда форматов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Uma ferramenta muito fácil para digitalizar documentos e fotografias. Pode cortar e rodar. Pode imprimir as digitalizações, exportar para PDF, ou guardar em vários tipos de formatos de imagem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Bardzo prosty sposób na skanowanie dokumentów i zdjęć. Umożliwia kadrowanie i obracanie zdjęć, drukowanie, eksportowanie do formatu PDF oraz zapisywanie w wielu formatach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een heel makkelijke manier om zowel documenten als foto's te scannen. U kunt de lelijke delen van een foto wegsnijden en hem draaien als hij niet goed staat. U kunt uw scans afdrukken, exporteren naar pdf, of opslaan in een reeks afbeeldingsbestandsoorten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">En enkel måte å skanne dokumenter og bilder på. Du kan skjære bort uønskede deler og rotere bilder hvis de skannes inn feil vei. Skannede elementer kan skrives ut, eksporteres i pdf-format og lagres i ulike bildeformater.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Cara paling mudah mengimbas kedua-dua dokumen dan gambar. Anda boleh kerat bahagian foto yang tidak dikehendaki atau putar ia jika berada pada kedudukan yang salah. Anda boleh cetak imbasan anda, eksport ia ke pdf, atau simpan ia dengan sejumlah besar format imej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Tikrai labai lengvas būdas skenuoti ir dokumentus, ir nuotraukas. Galite iškirpti blogas nuotraukos puses ir ją pasukti, jei ji neteisingai atvaizduojama. Galite spausdinti savo skenavimus, eksportuoti juos į pdf, ar įrašyti juos daugeliu paveikslų formatų.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">문서나 사진을 스캐닝하는 쉬운 방법입니다. 사진에서 쓰지 않는 부분을 잘라내거나 방향이 틀리면 돌려서 바로잡을 수 있습니다. 스캐닝한 것을 출력하거나, pdf 파일로 내보내거나, 여러 가지 형식으로 저장할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">ドキュメントや写真を本当に簡単な方法でスキャンします。写真の不要な部分を切り取ったり、間違った方向に向いている場合は回転できます。スキャンしたものを印刷、PDFへのエクスポート、多くの画像フォーマットに保存することができます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Un modo molto semplice per acquisire documenti e foto. È possibile ritagliare le parti non necessarie di una foto e ruotarla se è nel verso sbagliato. È anche possibile stampare i file acquisiti esportarli in formato PDF o salvarli in vari formati di immagine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Cara mudah untuk memindai dokumen dan foto. Anda dapat membuang bagian yang jelek dari suatu foto dan memutarnya bila itu terbalik. Anda dapat mencetak pindaian Anda, mengekspor ke pdf, atau menyimpan ke sejumlah format berkas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Igazán egyszerű megoldás dokumentumok és fényképek szkennelésére. Levághatja a képek fölösleges részeit, és elforgathatja azokat. Kinyomtathatja, PDF-be vagy számos képformátumba is exportálhatja a szkennelt dokumentumokat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Istinski jednostavan način skeniranja dokumenata i fotografija. Možete izrezati loše dijelove fotografija i zakrenuti ih ako su pogrešno okrenute. Možete ispisati vaše skenirane dokumente ili fotografije, izvesti ih u pdf ili ih spremiti u različite slikovne formate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">דרך פשוטה ביותר לסריקת מסמכים ותמונות. ניתן לגזור את החלקים שאינם נחוצים בתמונה ולהטות אם היא בכיוון הלא נכון. ניתן להדפיס את הסריקות שלך, לייצא אותן ל־PDF או לשמור אותן במגוון רחב של תסדירי תמונה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Un xeito ben sinxelo de escanear documentos e imaxes. Pode recortar as partes malas dunha foto e rotala se está do revés. Pode imprimir os escaneos, exportalos a un PDF ou gardalos en varios formatos de imaxe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Seo dòigh glè fhurasta gus an dà chuid sgrìobhainnean is dealbhan a sganadh. 'S urrainn dhut na pàirtean dona dhen dhealbh a bhearradh air falbh agus an dealbh a chuairteachadh mur eil a' chomhair cheart air. 'S urrainn dhut na sganaich thu a chlò-bhualadh, às-phortadh gu PDF no a shàbhaladh ann an taghadh de fhòrmatan deilbh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Une façon très simple de numériser à la fois documents et photos. Vous pouvez recadrer une photo et la faire pivoter si elle est dans le mauvais sens. Vous pouvez imprimer vos numérisations, les exporter au format pdf ou les enregistrer dans d'autres formats d'image.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr_CA">Une façon très simple de numériser à la fois documents et photos. Vous pouvez recadrer une photo et la faire pivoter si elle est dans le mauvais sens. Vous pouvez imprimer vos numérisations, les exporter au format pdf ou les enregistrer dans d'autres formats d'image.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Helppo tapa lukea (skannata) asiakirjoja ja valokuvia. Voit rajata huonot osat valokuvista pois tai kääntää niitä. Luettuja kuvia voidaan tulostaa, viedä PDF-muotoon tai tallentaa eri kuvamuodoissa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Modu benetan erraza dokumentuak zein argazkiak eskaneatzeko. Argazki baten parte txarrak ebaki eta</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Escanee documentos y fotos con suma sencillez. Es posible recortar las partes no deseadas de una foto y girarla si quedó al revés. Luego podrá imprimir las digitalizaciones, exportarlas a PDF o guardarlas en diversos formatos de imagen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">A really easy way to scan both documents and photos. You can crop out the bad parts of a photo and rotate it if it is the wrong way round. You can print your scans, export them to PDF or save them in a range of image formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Eine ganz einfache Methode, um sowohl Dokumente als auch Fotos zu scannen. Unbrauchbare Teile eines Fotos können abgeschnitten werden, es kann gedreht werden, falls es verkehrt herum liegt. Die Scans können gedruckt, als PDF-Dokument exportiert oder in einer Anzahl verschiedener Bildformate gespeichert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">En virkelig nem måde at skanne både dokumenter og billeder. Du kan beskære de uønskede dele fra et billede og rotere det, hvis det vender forkert. Du kan udskrive dine skanninger, eksportere dem til pdf eller gemme dem i en række billedformater.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Skutečně snadné skenování dokumentů a fotek, které mimo jiné nabízí šikovné úpravy. Vystřihněte nechtěné části fotografie a přetočte ji klidně o 360 stupňů! Až budete hotovy, materiál si nechtě vytisknout, převést do pdf, nebo uložit v rozmanité škále formátů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Una manera realment senzilla d'escanejar tant documents com fotos. Podeu retallar les parts dolentes d'una foto o rotar-la si està en la posició incorrecta.  Podeu imprimir els vostres escanejos, exportar-los a pdf, o desar-los en diversos formats d'imatge.</p>
    <p>
      Simple Scan uses the SANE framework to support most existing scanners.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">簡易掃描使用 SANE 框架以支援大部分現存掃描器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">簡易掃描使用 SANE 框架以支援大部分現存掃描器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">扫描易使用 SANE 框架支持大多数现有的扫描仪。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Для роботи із більшістю сканерів у Simple Scan використовуються бібліотеки SANE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Basit Tarayıcı mevcut bir çok tarayıcı desteği için SANE altyapısını kullanır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Simple Scan använder ramverket SANE för att hantera de flesta skannrar som finns på marknaden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Обично скенирање користи САНЕ радни оквир да би додатно подржао већину тренутних скенера.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Enostavno optično branje zahteva ogrodje SANE, da lahko podpira večino obstoječih optičnih bralnikov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Aplikácia Jednoduché skenovanie využíva rozhranie SANE, kvôli podpore väčšiny existujúcich skenerov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Простое сканирование использует фреймворк SANE для поддержки большинства существующих сканеров.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Simple Scan usa a estrutura SANE para suportar a maior parte dos scanners atuais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program Simple Scan używa mechanizmu SANE do obsługi większości istniejących skanerów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Simple Scan gebruikt het SANE-kader om de meeste scanners te kunnen gebruiken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Simple Scan bruker rammeverket SANE til å støtte de vanligste skannerne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengimbas Ringkas menggunakan bingkai kerja SANE untuk menyokong kebanyakan pengimbas sedia ada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Paprastas skenavimas naudoja SANE karkasą, kad palaikytų daugelį esamų skenerių.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">심플 스캔은 현존하는 거의 모든 스캐너들을 지원하는 SANE 프레임워크를 사용합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">シンプル スキャンはSANE フレームワークを採用しており、多数の既存スキャナに対応しています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Simple Scan usa il framework SANE per supportare il maggior numero di scanner esistenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Simple Scan memakai framework SANE untuk mendukung kebanyakan pemindai yang ada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Simple Scan a SANE keretrendszert használja a legtöbb létező szkenner támogatása érdekében.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Skeniranje dokumenata koristi SANE radni okvir za podršku većine postojećih skenera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">סריקה פשוטה משתמשת בסביבת העבודה SANE לטובת תמיכה ברוב הסורקים הזמינים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Escáner Sinxelo usa o marco de traballo de SANE para ser compatíbel coa maioría de escáneres existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Cleachdaidh Sganadh simplidh a' framework SANE gus taic a thoirt dhan mhòrchuid a sganairean a tha ann.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Simple Scan utilise la structure logicielle de SANE pour prendre en charge la plupart des périphériques de numérisation existants.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr_CA">Simple Scan utilise la structure logicielle de SANE pour prendre en charge la plupart des périphériques de numérisation existants.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tämä sovellus käyttää SANE-kehystä tukeakseen useimpia olemassa olevia kuvanlukijoita.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Simple Scan SANE framework erabiltzen du dauden eskaner gehienei sostengua emateko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Simple Scan emplea el marco SANE para compatibilidad con la mayoría de los escáneres existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Simple Scan uses the SANE framework which supports most existing scanners.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Simple Scan verwendet das SANE-Programmiergerüst für die Unterstützung der meisten verfügbaren Scanner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Simpel skanning bruger SANE-rammeværket for at understøtte flest mulige skannere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Simple Scan používá SANE framework, aby pokryl co největší množství scannerů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Simple Scan fa servir l'entorn SANE per donar suport a la major part dels escàners existents.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">https://launchpadlibrarian.net/203209644/simple-scan.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://launchpad.net/simple-scan</url>
  <update_contact>robert.ancell_AT_canonical.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">simple-scan</translation>
</component>
